<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- produced for the bleb.org TV system at Fri Apr  3 07:21:25 2020 -->
<channel id="cbbc" source="XMLTV" date="08/04/2020">
  <programme>
<end>0700</end>
<start>0600</start>
<desc>This is CBBC! Join the CBBC crew for all your favourite programmes. Tune into CBBC every day from 7.00am.</desc>
<title>This is CBBC!</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Mutiny on the Pitch. Animated adventures of a young aardvark. The Lakewood Elementary soccer team has had enough of Francine's bossy behaviour. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<start>0700</start>
<end>0715</end>
<title>Arthur</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
<end>0725</end>
<start>0715</start>
<desc>Wonder Sausage. Animated series. Walter realises a sausage has a strange hypnotic effect on Gnasher so uses it to make him perform his every whim. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0735</end>
<desc>Sorry Mr Sun. Lennon offends the sun, causing a blackout in Townopolis. Both Gluko and Lennon must work on their apologies to save the town and soothe their consciences. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<start>0725</start>
<title>Little Big Awesome</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0750</end>
<start>0735</start>
<desc>The Cheesy Diary. Boy discovers that somebody is writing a fantasy novel inside his diary. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Class Dismissed</title>
<end>0805</end>
<desc>Child Care Issues. Comedy series. New teaching assistant Mr Nappy discovers that being in a school and taking care of three babies doesn't mix. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<start>0750</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0830</end>
<desc>Dance-Zilla. Reality-style drama series. Richelle is back and A-Troupe desperately hopes she will bring down Miss Angela. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<start>0805</start>
<title>The Next Step</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0830</start>
<desc>Episode 3. Four junior bakers attempt to create a show-stopping vegetable cake. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<end>0900</end>
<title>Junior Bake Off</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0915</end>
<desc>Slime Party. The Crafters get creative to make incredible art and fantastic food ready for an amazing party - and you're all invited! Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<start>0900</start>
<title>Craft Party</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Newsround</title>
<end>0925</end>
<start>0915</start>
<desc>08/04/2020. Topical news magazine for children. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0925</start>
<desc>In 2015, the cast of The Next Step began a tour across Canada. For the fans who had tickets to those performances it was a chance to see their favourite dancers in person. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<end>1045</end>
<title>The Next Step Live - The Movie</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1110</end>
<start>1045</start>
<desc>Everlasting Energy. Dick and Dom's quest takes them into the frazzling, windy and fast-flowing world of renewable energy. They head deep into the searing Nevada desert. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<title>Absolute Genius: Monster Builds</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>The Solar Show. Tim and Naomi search the natural world for all things weird. Featuring a solar death ray that's frying birds mid-flight, and a shocking new discovery. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<start>1110</start>
<end>1125</end>
<title>Wild &amp; Weird</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1155</end>
<desc>Chantry v St Joseph's. Chantry Primary take on St Joseph's in a quiz show to win the title of Top Class. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<start>1125</start>
<title>Top Class</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>The Dumping Ground: I'm Tyler</title>
<desc>Tyler. Dumping Ground characters gather to watch videos made by Ashdene Ridge residents about their lives there. This time, it is Tyler's turn. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<start>1155</start>
<end>1210</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Newsround</title>
<start>1210</start>
<desc>08/04/2020. Topical news magazine for children. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<end>1215</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Millie Inbetween</title>
<end>1245</end>
<desc>So Long Sunnyshopper. Comedy drama series. When Mum is made redundant from her job at Sunnyshopper, the family are supportive - until she starts a regime of frenzied tidying. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<start>1215</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Millie Inbetween</title>
<end>1310</end>
<desc>Meatballs. Comedy drama series. It's parents' evening, but Millie is desperate to prevent Mum and Dad seeing her English teacher, Miss Knope. She turns to Lauren for help. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<start>1245</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Gym Stars</title>
<start>1310</start>
<desc>Life Changes. Series following young gymnasts. Can Cameron shine in his dance show at school and still keep up with training in the gym? Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<end>1330</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Breaking Free. Series following young gymnasts. Joe, Olly and Oscar decide to become film producers for the day and create their own Free-G video to post online. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<start>1330</start>
<end>1350</end>
<title>Gym Stars</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Gym Stars</title>
<desc>A Star is Born. Series following young gymnasts. Abi and her fellow team mate Sophie train for the annual gala, where they hope to wow the audience. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<start>1350</start>
<end>1410</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1440</end>
<desc>Rugby Den. Joe and Lauren get the help of experts to design dream dens for children. Will needs a rugby den to keep him in the game. Also in HD. [S,SL]</desc>
<start>1410</start>
<title>The Dengineers</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1440</start>
<desc>Time to Say Goodbye. Nate is in turmoil with Chloe and the boys, then Sasha makes him an offer he can't refuse. Also in HD. [S,SL]</desc>
<end>1510</end>
<title>Almost Never</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Danger Mouse</title>
<end>1520</end>
<start>1510</start>
<desc>The World Wide Spider. Animated series. Danger Mouse has to face his only fear when Penfold accidentally awakens a gigantic spider. Also in HD. [S,AD]</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Diddy Bits</title>
<end>1525</end>
<desc>Diddy Robot Wars. Clips from Diddy Dick and Dom's television channel. Featuring music with another episode of the Diddy Choir. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<start>1520</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Dinmaker Diva. Animated series. The gang are fed up with dinner lady Olive's inedible school dinners. They learn she used to be a singer and try to persuade her to change career. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<start>1525</start>
<end>1535</end>
<title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Little Big Awesome</title>
<start>1535</start>
<desc>Sorry Mr Sun. Lennon offends the sun, causing a blackout in Townopolis. Both Gluko and Lennon must work on their apologies to save the town and soothe their consciences. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<end>1550</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1550</start>
<desc>The Cheesy Diary. Boy discovers that somebody is writing a fantasy novel inside his diary. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<end>1600</end>
<title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Newsround</title>
<end>1605</end>
<desc>08/04/2020. Topical news magazine for children. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<start>1600</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1615</end>
<desc>You Could Take a Lift to Space? What would happen if there really was a lift that took you all the way up to space? Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<start>1605</start>
<title>Hey You What If?</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Odd Squad</title>
<end>1625</end>
<desc>The Scientist. Oona gets zapped into an alternate dimension. Also in HD. [S,AD]</desc>
<start>1615</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1640</end>
<desc>Golden Voice. Comedy series. Pop star Zoe Now arrives to open the new reception. Joy asks Danny and Mick to welcome her, but their attempts at hospitality leave her without a voice. Also in HD. [S,AD]</desc>
<start>1625</start>
<title>Danny and Mick</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Kara, Willow and Honey. James uses some high-tech gear to help a vomiting dog, Cat performs surgery on a rat, and Cheryl clips the nails of a very nervous pooch. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<start>1640</start>
<end>1700</end>
<title>The Pets Factor</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1700</start>
<desc>Battle of the Lesser Bands. Ginger is hoping for the perfect night, while Chris hopes for the perfect day. Also in HD. [S,AD]</desc>
<end>1725</end>
<title>Secret Life of Boys</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1750</end>
<start>1725</start>
<desc>Ready For Battle. Jenny prepares for the battle that Hillside will be and re-lives the more painful moments of her past. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<title>New: My Perfect Landing</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1750</start>
<desc>Stepping Into the Unknown. It's the British Trampoline Championships and Theo is competing for the first time in a synchro pair. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<end>1815</end>
<title>New: Gym Stars</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>What Happened Next? Join the doctors for a special episode as they revisit with Ouchers from across the last seven series to find out how they are doing now. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<start>1815</start>
<end>1845</end>
<title>Operation Ouch!</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Lindsey and the Royal Yacht. Lindsey boards the Royal Yacht Britannia to help with some spring cleaning and bakes a special birthday cake. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<start>1845</start>
<end>1855</end>
<title>Blue Peter Bites</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1855</start>
<desc>Exceptional Explorers. A special episode looking at explorers, from the Vikings' first small steps on American soil to humankind's first giant leaps on the moon. Also in HD. [S,AD]</desc>
<end>1925</end>
<title>Horrible Histories</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>My Perfect Landing</title>
<desc>Ready For Battle. Jenny prepares for the battle that Hillside will be and re-lives the more painful moments of her past. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<start>1925</start>
<end>1945</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Hank Zipzer</title>
<end>2010</end>
<start>1945</start>
<desc>The Lucky Socks. The school announces its annual house sport and quiz competition, and Hank finds himself forced to try out for the Yellow House softball team. Also in HD. [S,AD]</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>2010</start>
<desc>Stepping Into the Unknown. It's the British Trampoline Championships and Theo is competing for the first time in a synchro pair. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<end>2035</end>
<title>Gym Stars</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Battle of the Lesser Bands. Ginger is hoping for the perfect night, while Chris hopes for the perfect day. Also in HD. [S,AD]</desc>
<start>2035</start>
<end>2100</end>
<title>Secret Life of Boys</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0000</end>
<start>2100</start>
<desc>This is CBBC! Join the CBBC crew for all your favourite programmes. Tune into CBBC every day from 7.00am.</desc>
<title>This is CBBC!</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0600</end>
<start>0000</start>
<desc>This is CBBC! Join the CBBC crew for all your favourite programmes. Tune into CBBC every day from 7.00am.</desc>
<title>This is CBBC!</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0600</start>
<desc>This is CBBC! Join the CBBC crew for all your favourite programmes. Tune into CBBC every day from 7.00am.</desc>
<end>0700</end>
<title>This is CBBC!</title>
  </programme>
</channel>
