<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- produced for the bleb.org TV system at Fri Apr  3 07:21:58 2020 -->
<channel id="e4" source="XMLTV" date="08/04/2020">
  <programme>
<subtitle>Game On</subtitle>
<title>Rules of Engagement</title>
<start>0600</start>
<desc>Audrey is upset when Jeff doesn't react to her recent promotion at work and assumes that he is more interested in the Knicks than in her.</desc>
<end>0630</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0700</end>
<desc>Russell thinks that he's found the perfect girl when she keeps making sexy comments to him, while Audrey worries about her marriage.</desc>
<start>0630</start>
<title>Rules of Engagement</title>
<subtitle>Jeff's Wooby</subtitle>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0700</start>
<desc>After Marshall sees a documentary about an island in the Pacific that is used as a landfill site, he becomes determined to save the environment. (S6 Ep17/24)</desc>
<end>0730</end>
<subtitle>Garbage Island</subtitle>
<title>How I Met Your Mother</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>A Change of Heart</subtitle>
<title>How I Met Your Mother</title>
<start>0730</start>
<desc>The friends have health checks in the wake of Marshall's dad's fatal heart attack. Robin dates a man called Scooby who reminds the gang of a dog. (S6 Ep18/24)</desc>
<end>0800</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>The Perfect Storm</subtitle>
<title>Melissa &amp; Joey</title>
<start>0800</start>
<desc>Mel grounds Lennox because she's failing chemistry, but when Mel's father Senator Russell Burke shows up unexpectedly, he undermines her authority. (S1 Ep5/30)</desc>
<end>0830</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Melissa &amp; Joey</title>
<subtitle>Spies and Lies</subtitle>
<end>0900</end>
<desc>Mel catches Joe having secret meetings in the basement with a girl called Tessa, and discovers that they're on a manhunt for her brother-in-law, Lewis Scanlon. (S1 Ep6/30)</desc>
<start>0830</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0900</start>
<desc>Molly offers her wisdom to Samuel, who aspires to be a stand-up comedian. And Molly's advice to Harry makes him challenge his over-protective mother. (S4 Ep12)</desc>
<end>0930</end>
<title>Mike &amp; Molly</title>
<subtitle>Open Mike Night</subtitle>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>When Victoria brings home a new boyfriend called James, the entire family wonders whether she might have found 'The One' at last. (S4 Ep13)</desc>
<start>0930</start>
<end>1000</end>
<subtitle>Rich Man, Poor Girl</subtitle>
<title>Mike &amp; Molly</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>The Excelsior Acquisition</subtitle>
<title>The Big Bang Theory</title>
<start>1000</start>
<desc>Sheldon is summoned to court for driving through a red light. He misses the chance to meet Stan Lee and riles the judge. Will he go to prison? (S3 Ep16/23)</desc>
<end>1030</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>The Precious Fragmentation</subtitle>
<title>The Big Bang Theory</title>
<end>1100</end>
<desc>The gang squabble over a ring that they believe was used in The Lord of the Rings movies, while Sheldon seems to be turning into Gollum. (S3 Ep17/23)</desc>
<start>1030</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>The Goldbergs</title>
<subtitle>There Can Be Only One Highlander Club</subtitle>
<desc>Adam and Johnny Atkins compete to become head of the Highlander Club at school, though Beverly would prefer them to bond. (S6 Ep16)</desc>
<start>1100</start>
<end>1130</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1200</end>
<desc>Erica, Barry and Adam are unhappy when their distant relative Gleb visits from Russia, until they realise he can make their lives easier. (S6 Ep17/23)</desc>
<start>1130</start>
<title>The Goldbergs</title>
<subtitle>Our Perfect Strangers</subtitle>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1230</end>
<desc>Coral Palms (Part 3/3): The team go on a road trip to help Peralta and Holt take down crime boss Jimmy Figgis but their plan is hindered by an unforeseen injury. (S4 Ep3/22)</desc>
<start>1200</start>
<title>Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1300</end>
<desc>Holt looks for ways to improve the team's morale, while Santiago is filled with curiosity when Diaz starts to take long breaks from her desk. (S4 Ep4/22)</desc>
<start>1230</start>
<subtitle>The Night Shift</subtitle>
<title>Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1330</end>
<start>1300</start>
<desc>Sheldon pays a surprise visit to his mother in Houston and is forced to confront a new reality. Raj throws a murder mystery-themed dinner party. (S7 Ep18/24)</desc>
<subtitle>The Mommy Observation</subtitle>
<title>The Big Bang Theory</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>The Indecision Amalgamation</subtitle>
<title>The Big Bang Theory</title>
<end>1400</end>
<start>1330</start>
<desc>Raj faces a dating dilemma, Penny can't decide whether to accept a role in a terrible film, and Sheldon chooses between two gaming systems. (S7 Ep19/24)</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Mel asks Joe to act as translator when she has a meeting with a Japanese businessman, but once they all get together for dinner, things turn awkward. (S1 Ep15/30)</desc>
<start>1400</start>
<end>1430</end>
<subtitle>Lost in Translation</subtitle>
<title>Melissa &amp; Joey</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Despite everything that has happened to him over the past year, Joe decides to go to his college reunion and meet up with his former classmates. (S1 Ep16/30)</desc>
<start>1430</start>
<end>1500</end>
<subtitle>Joe Versus the Reunion</subtitle>
<title>Melissa &amp; Joey</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>To Have and Withhold</subtitle>
<title>Mike &amp; Molly</title>
<end>1530</end>
<start>1500</start>
<desc>Molly panics when she gets a bad case of writer's block because she might lose the big advance for her book if she can't cure it in a hurry. (S5 Ep2)</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1600</end>
<desc>'Tis the Season to Be Molly: Mike assures Molly he'll be home in time for Christmas Eve dinner, but things go awry when he and Carl end up in the back of a stolen truck. (S5 Ep3)</desc>
<start>1530</start>
<title>Mike &amp; Molly</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Mini Murray</subtitle>
<title>The Goldbergs</title>
<end>1630</end>
<desc>Barry wants money to buy an expensive new pair of basketball shoes, so Murray hires him to work at his furniture shop so he can earn it. (S1 Ep3/23)</desc>
<start>1600</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>The Goldbergs</title>
<subtitle>Why're You Hitting Yourself?</subtitle>
<end>1700</end>
<start>1630</start>
<desc>Determined to get Pops to settle down, Beverly plays matchmaker for her father and pairs him up with a woman called Sophia. (S1 Ep4/23)</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
<subtitle>The Audit</subtitle>
<end>1730</end>
<start>1700</start>
<desc>One of the precincts in the area must be closed, so an evaluation takes place. The team find out that the auditor is Santiago's ex-boyfriend, Teddy. (S4 Ep13/22)</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1800</end>
<start>1730</start>
<desc>A burglary on the set of a TV detective show distracts Peralta and Diaz from the precinct's on-going evaluation as a new auditor takes over. (S4 Ep14/22)</desc>
<title>Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
<subtitle>Serve &amp; Protect</subtitle>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>The Big Bang Theory</title>
<subtitle>The Hook-Up Reverberation</subtitle>
<desc>Raj's honesty about his past comes back to haunt him when his girlfriend Emily gives Penny the cold shoulder. The guys consider an investment. (S8 Ep4/24)</desc>
<start>1800</start>
<end>1830</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>The Big Bang Theory</title>
<subtitle>The Focus Attenuation</subtitle>
<desc>The guys attempt to invent something of scientific importance, but only come up with new and enjoyable ways to procrastinate. (S8 Ep5/24)</desc>
<start>1830</start>
<end>1900</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1900</start>
<desc>Former Hollyoaks star Kieron Richardson revisits the soap's classic villains. Cameron Campbell takes his daughter, Peri, and her family hostage. Will they be found before it's too late?</desc>
<end>1930</end>
<title>Hollyoaks Favourites</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>New: Man with a Plan</title>
<start>1930</start>
<desc>Brand new series - April Fools: When Adam insists that pranks are harmless fun, Andi creates an elaborate hoax to teach him a lesson. (S2 Ep16)</desc>
<end>2000</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>2030</end>
<start>2000</start>
<desc>Brand new series - The Beverly Goldberg Cookbook: Part 2: When a publisher shows interest in her recipes, Beverly prepares to finally realise her dream of writing a cookbook. (S7 Ep8)</desc>
<title>New: The Goldbergs</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>2030</start>
<desc>Brand new series - Friendsgiving: CB celebrates Thanksgiving by having all of William Penn rally around him after a cooking incident at his house. (S2 Ep8)</desc>
<end>2100</end>
<title>New: Schooled</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Celebrity Gogglebox</title>
<end>2200</end>
<desc>From Love Island to The Family Brain Game, what do Oti Mabuse, Rachel Riley, Rylan Clark-Neal, Denise van Outen, Emily Atack, Nick Grimshaw and other famous faces think of our top TV? (Ep2)</desc>
<start>2100</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>New: Zoey's Extraordinary Playlist</title>
<start>2200</start>
<desc>Brand new series - Zoey's Extraordinary Night Out: Things get complicated for Zoey at Simon's engagement party. Maggie has a night out alone, but it doesn't go as planned. (Ep6/12)</desc>
<end>2300</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>When Sheldon has to teach a course at the university, Howard enrols in his class. Tension is brewing between Penny and Bernadette. (S8 Ep2/24)</desc>
<start>2300</start>
<end>2330</end>
<title>The Big Bang Theory</title>
<subtitle>The Junior Professor Solution</subtitle>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0000</end>
<start>2330</start>
<desc>Howard's nervous when Nasa ask him to throw the first pitch at a baseball game. Sheldon claims his and Amy's relationship is the best in the gang. (S8 Ep3/24)</desc>
<title>The Big Bang Theory</title>
<subtitle>The First Pitch Insufficiency</subtitle>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0000</start>
<desc>What do Britain's sharpest armchair critics think of Our Planet, This Morning, Britain's Got Talent, Line of Duty, Blind Date, and 24 Hours in Police Custody? (S13 Ep8) [SL]</desc>
<end>0100</end>
<title>Gogglebox</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Celebrity Gogglebox</title>
<end>0205</end>
<start>0100</start>
<desc>From Love Island to The Family Brain Game, what do Oti Mabuse, Rachel Riley, Rylan Clark-Neal, Denise van Outen, Emily Atack, Nick Grimshaw and other famous faces think of our top TV? (Ep2)</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0205</start>
<desc>Brand new series - The Beverly Goldberg Cookbook: Part 2: When a publisher shows interest in her recipes, Beverly prepares to finally realise her dream of writing a cookbook. (S7 Ep8)</desc>
<end>0230</end>
<title>The Goldbergs</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0255</end>
<start>0230</start>
<desc>Brand new series - Friendsgiving: CB celebrates Thanksgiving by having all of William Penn rally around him after a cooking incident at his house. (S2 Ep8)</desc>
<title>Schooled</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Zoey's Extraordinary Playlist</title>
<end>0345</end>
<desc>Brand new series - Zoey's Extraordinary Night Out: Things get complicated for Zoey at Simon's engagement party. Maggie has a night out alone, but it doesn't go as planned. (Ep6/12)</desc>
<start>0255</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>The Big Bang Theory</title>
<subtitle>The Excelsior Acquisition</subtitle>
<end>0410</end>
<start>0345</start>
<desc>Sheldon is summoned to court for driving through a red light. He misses the chance to meet Stan Lee and riles the judge. Will he go to prison? (S3 Ep16/23)</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>The Big Bang Theory</title>
<subtitle>The Precious Fragmentation</subtitle>
<end>0435</end>
<start>0410</start>
<desc>The gang squabble over a ring that they believe was used in The Lord of the Rings movies, while Sheldon seems to be turning into Gollum. (S3 Ep17/23)</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0500</end>
<desc>After Marshall sees a documentary about an island in the Pacific that is used as a landfill site, he becomes determined to save the environment. (S6 Ep17/24)</desc>
<start>0435</start>
<subtitle>Garbage Island</subtitle>
<title>How I Met Your Mother</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>How I Met Your Mother</title>
<subtitle>A Change of Heart</subtitle>
<start>0500</start>
<desc>The friends have health checks in the wake of Marshall's dad's fatal heart attack. Robin dates a man called Scooby who reminds the gang of a dog. (S6 Ep18/24)</desc>
<end>0600</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Flirting with Disaster</subtitle>
<title>Rules of Engagement</title>
<end>0630</end>
<desc>When Jeff's snoring finally becomes unbearable, Audrey decides that they should sleep in separate bedrooms, but Jeff soon takes advantage of the situation.</desc>
<start>0600</start>
  </programme>
</channel>
