<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- produced for the bleb.org TV system at Fri Apr  3 07:22:47 2020 -->
<channel id="more4" source="XMLTV" date="08/04/2020">
  <programme>
<title>Teleshopping</title>
<desc>Teleshopping.</desc>
<start>0340</start>
<end>0700</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Teleshopping</title>
<end>0855</end>
<start>0700</start>
<desc>Teleshopping.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Kirstie's Vintage Gems</title>
<end>0915</end>
<start>0855</start>
<desc>Master sculptor and gilder Adam Williamson shows Kirstie Allsopp how easy it is to apply gold leaf to a second-hand picture frame, giving it that luxury look.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>A Place in the Sun: Winter Sun</title>
<end>1005</end>
<desc>Recently divorced Rajula plans to buy a place in southern Spain to enjoy with her twin sons and friends. Sara Damergi shows her what's on the market near the pretty coastal town of Nerja.</desc>
<start>0915</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>A Place in the Sun: Winter Sun</title>
<end>1105</end>
<desc>Sara Damergi takes Viv and Steve house-hunting on Spain's northern Costa Blanca. With a budget of £130,000, they are looking for a holiday home that they can eventually retire to.</desc>
<start>1005</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Find It, Fix It, Flog It</title>
<desc>Henry Cole and Max McMurdo travel the length of Britain looking for items to fix up and flog. In Wales, picks include an oil dispenser, a chaise longue and a catamaran. (S2 Ep5/25)</desc>
<start>1105</start>
<end>1210</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Find It, Fix It, Flog It</title>
<desc>Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien find, fix and flog unwanted possessions. This episode includes an old cheese press. And a 1980s motorbike almost gets the better of Henry and Guy. (S2 Ep11/25)</desc>
<start>1210</start>
<end>1315</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Escape to the Chateau: DIY</title>
<desc>Tim and Rebecca struggle to get their kilometre-long driveway ready for high-end sports cars. Amy and Marc unearth a medieval fireplace. Dick checks in with Ben and Billie. (S3 Ep3)</desc>
<start>1315</start>
<end>1420</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1450</end>
<start>1420</start>
<desc>This time Four in a Bed becomes Four in a Camp Bed, as four sets of campsite proprietors battle it out. The first visit is to Amber's Bell Tent Camping in north Norfolk.</desc>
<title>Four in a Bed</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Four in a Bed</title>
<start>1450</start>
<desc>The second visit is to Park Farm Camping and Caravan Site in Norfolk where husband-and-wife team Derek and Julie Nice want their back-to-basics, family-friendly glamping site to win.</desc>
<end>1520</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Four in a Bed</title>
<end>1550</end>
<desc>The third visit of the competition is to 500-year-old Layer Marney Tower, in Essex, where posh hosts Nick and Sheila Charrington unzip their luxury canvas lodges for scrutiny.</desc>
<start>1520</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1625</end>
<start>1550</start>
<desc>The fourth day of the competition is at the Foxhunter Park in Kent, where gregarious brother-and-sister team Jane Stacey and Russell Saunders own a luxury caravanning site.</desc>
<title>Four in a Bed</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1625</start>
<desc>Four in a Bed became Four in a Camp Bed for this competition, which saw campsite proprietors battle to be named best value. It's the last day and a few scores need settling.</desc>
<end>1655</end>
<title>Four in a Bed</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>A couple of expats swap Chelmsford for Charente, Spain's newest seafood restaurant begins to make a name for itself, and some Londoners host a traditional tea party at their French B&amp;B.</desc>
<start>1655</start>
<end>1755</end>
<title>A New Life in the Sun</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1855</end>
<start>1755</start>
<desc>In North Yorkshire, Tim and Fuzz restore Helen's 1974 Mk1 Ford Capri, which is in so many pieces it's almost impossible to tell what it is. (S6 Ep10/10)</desc>
<subtitle>Ford Capri Mk1</subtitle>
<title>Car S.O.S</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1855</start>
<desc>Rebecca visits Angel for tips on renovating the kitchen. Amy and Marc transform a bathroom that's stuck in a 1970s time-warp. Ben and Billie prepare for Billie's brother's wedding. (S3 Ep4)</desc>
<end>1955</end>
<title>Escape to the Chateau: DIY</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Fred and Saffron build a home in the Peak District on a 30 degree slope, with the top floor in plain sight and two post-industrial style floors buried into the thick limestone below. (Ep7)</desc>
<start>1955</start>
<end>2100</end>
<title>Grand Designs</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>2200</end>
<start>2100</start>
<desc>Brand new series: Charlie's in Derbyshire with Sean and Jill who aim to build a traditional home with a contemporary twist. But can their ambitious plans withstand the challenges? (S9 Ep4)</desc>
<title>New: Building the Dream</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>2200</start>
<desc>Brand new series: Tony and Tania want a million-dollar house on a $400,000 budget. Working off handshake deals with the architect and builder, will their dream home be finished? (S8 Ep4)</desc>
<end>2305</end>
<title>New: Grand Designs Australia</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0010</end>
<desc>This episode features patients who fell in love with their partners at first sight, including Henry and Audrey, who've been married for nearly 70 years. (S9 Ep2/8)</desc>
<start>2305</start>
<title>24 Hours in A&amp;E</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown</title>
<end>0115</end>
<start>0010</start>
<desc>Jimmy Carr hosts. Sean Lock and Bob Mortimer take on guest captain Sarah Millican and Katherine Ryan with Alex Horne and the Horne Section in Dictionary Corner. (S7 Ep7/17)</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0215</end>
<desc>Brand new series: Charlie's in Derbyshire with Sean and Jill who aim to build a traditional home with a contemporary twist. But can their ambitious plans withstand the challenges? (S9 Ep4)</desc>
<start>0115</start>
<title>Building the Dream</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0215</start>
<desc>This episode features patients who fell in love with their partners at first sight, including Henry and Audrey, who've been married for nearly 70 years. (S9 Ep2/8)</desc>
<end>0320</end>
<title>24 Hours in A&amp;E</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Food Unwrapped</title>
<end>0350</end>
<start>0320</start>
<desc>The team investigate how supermarkets get the iced writing so perfect on birthday cakes, the popularity of the soy bean, and the growing trend for hemp-based food products. (S17 Ep2)</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0700</end>
<desc>Teleshopping.</desc>
<start>0350</start>
<title>Teleshopping</title>
  </programme>
</channel>
