<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- produced for the bleb.org TV system at Thu Apr  2 09:45:06 2020 -->
<channel id="p_itv2" source="XMLTV" date="08/04/2020">
  <programme>
<desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
<title>Teleshopping</title>
<end>0700</end>
<start>0330</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0700</start>
<end>0750</end>
<title>The Ellen DeGeneres Show</title>
<desc>Ellen is joined in the studio by American actress, comedian and writer Wanda Sykes and Bachelor in Paradise cast member Demi Burnett. S17 Ep9</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0750</start>
<end>0850</end>
<title>You've Been Framed! Gold: Top...</title>
<desc>...100 Kids. Harry Hill presents a special featuring the top 100 clips of kids from the You've Been Framed! vault. Featuring messy eaters, troublesome teens and sibling rivalries. S24 Ep11</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0850</start>
<desc>Harry Hill narrates more viewers' home videos. In this show, what David Cameron gets up to behind the bins at Chequers, and why Lorraine Kelly is testing Ross King's thongs. S26 Ep4</desc>
<title>You've Been Framed! Gold</title>
<end>0920</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Christmas Eve</subtitle>
<start>0920</start>
<title>Superstore</title>
<end>0950</end>
<desc>Amy brightens up Christmas Eve for the staff of Cloud 9. Glenn tries to increase Mateo's enthusiasm for Christmas. S3 Ep7</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Dina and Cheyenne snoop through the staffs' social media feeds after a controversial video is posted. Glenn suspects Mateo has been engaging in fraud. S3 Ep8</desc>
<title>Superstore</title>
<end>1015</end>
<start>0950</start>
<subtitle>Viral Video</subtitle>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1015</start>
<title>Dinner Date</title>
<end>1115</end>
<desc>Culinary dating show. Saidat from London picks three men to go on blind dates based on their menus, but will she fall for any of them? S5 Ep1</desc>
<subtitle>Saidat</subtitle>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Dating series with a difference. Three singletons try to win the affections of photographer Danielle by each buying her an outfit. S1 Ep4</desc>
<end>1215</end>
<title>Dress To Impress</title>
<start>1115</start>
<subtitle>Danielle</subtitle>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1320</end>
<title>Celebrity Catchphrase</title>
<desc>Stephen Mulhern hosts a celebrity special of the classic game show, with Sir Chris Hoy, Martine McCutcheon and Faye Tozer all trying to guess the familiar phrases.</desc>
<start>1215</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1320</start>
<desc>Mind-bending comedy from Harry Hill, inspired by viewers' home videos. Discover Matthew Kelly's method for removing a tattoo, and the fun to be had in Osama Bin Laden's old cave. S26 Ep5</desc>
<end>1350</end>
<title>You've Been Framed! Gold</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1445</end>
<title>The Ellen DeGeneres Show</title>
<desc>Ellen is joined in the studio by chat show royalty Oprah Winfrey. Plus, Lil Nas X talks to the host, before performing Panini. S17 Ep10</desc>
<start>1350</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1445</start>
<end>1550</end>
<title>Dinner Date</title>
<desc>Dating series with a delicious twist. Will from Essex dines with three lucky ladies, but which one will he come back to for seconds? S5 Ep2</desc>
<subtitle>Will</subtitle>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Dress To Impress</title>
<end>1650</end>
<desc>Fashion-themed dating series. Three more singletons compete in a series of shopping challenges in Cardiff to win the affections of sweet shop worker Jess. S1 Ep15</desc>
<start>1550</start>
<subtitle>Jess</subtitle>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>In the love lift this time are Bruno Mars tribute act Martin, duck lover Ollie, serial dater Nnamdi and skip driver Jack. S11 Ep6</desc>
<title>Take Me Out</title>
<end>1800</end>
<start>1650</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1800</start>
<desc>Narrated by Harry Hill. Including the illicit craze of face-changing that renders photo IDs useless, and a video so terrible it will stay in your mind forever. S26 Ep2</desc>
<title>You've Been Framed! Gold</title>
<end>1830</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>You've Been Framed! Gold</title>
<end>1900</end>
<desc>Surreal comedy as Harry Hill narrates more videos. Abi Titmuss tugs on a lemur, while Nadine Dorries puts the dry skin off her scalp to good use. S26 Ep3</desc>
<start>1830</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>A selection of hilarious home videos sent in by members of the public and presented in a much-loved format to entertain people of all ages. S27 Ep5</desc>
<end>1930</end>
<title>You've Been Framed! Gold</title>
<start>1900</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1930</start>
<desc>Harry Hill introduces the nation's favourite home video show. There is trouble with a language barrier for a bride in church and a nan gets run over by a fire engine. S27 Ep1</desc>
<end>2000</end>
<title>You've Been Framed! Gold</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>For Whom The Booty Calls</subtitle>
<end>2030</end>
<title>Two and a Half Men</title>
<desc>US comedy series. Walden joins a group for adoptive fathers and finds it to be a nice escape from Alan. S12 Ep11</desc>
<start>2000</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>A Beer-Battered Rip-Off</subtitle>
<end>2100</end>
<title>Two and a Half Men</title>
<desc>US comedy series. When Alan breaks up with their social worker to get back together with Lyndsey, Walden worries that it might affect Louis's adoption. S12 Ep12</desc>
<start>2030</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>This Little Piggy</subtitle>
<title>Family Guy</title>
<end>2130</end>
<desc>Meg is thrilled to be recruited as a model, but it turns out to be for a very specific type of modelling. Meanwhile, Brian accompanies Stewie on an adventure. S13 Ep10</desc>
<start>2100</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Quagmire's Mom</subtitle>
<title>Family Guy</title>
<end>2200</end>
<desc>Lois takes Peter to open a bank account, and they learn that his first name is actually Justin, which Peter adopts as the name of his younger 'bro-style' alter ego. S13 Ep11</desc>
<start>2130</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>2305</end>
<title>New: Joel Dommett: Finding Emo</title>
<desc>Joel Dommett's hilarious stand-up comedy special about teenage bands, friendships and relationships. Filmed during his sold out national tour.</desc>
<start>2200</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Encyclopedia Griffin</subtitle>
<title>Family Guy</title>
<end>2330</end>
<desc>Peter, Quagmire, Joe and Cleveland form a neighbourhood detective agency. Lois is worried about Chris's delusional new relationship. S13 Ep12</desc>
<start>2305</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Baking Bad</subtitle>
<title>Family Guy</title>
<end>0005</end>
<desc>Animated comedy. Lois and Peter go into business together and open a cookie store, but things get messy when Peter comes up with his own way to get more customers. S13 Ep3</desc>
<start>2330</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Big Stan on Campus</subtitle>
<desc>Animated comedy. When the CIA is forced to make cutbacks, Stan takes a position as a college campus security guard. Meanwhile, Roger opens a bed and breakfast. S11 Ep7</desc>
<title>American Dad!</title>
<end>0030</end>
<start>0005</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0030</start>
<desc>Animated comedy. Roger is forced to sell his attic bar after suffering a heart attack. A sexy new next door neighbour has an indecent proposal for Steve. S11 Ep1</desc>
<end>0055</end>
<title>American Dad!</title>
<subtitle>Roger Passes the Bar</subtitle>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Flush of Genius</subtitle>
<start>0055</start>
<desc>Cleveland Jr loses respect for his father when he falls off the toilet and gets a concussion, while Rallo is now tall enough to ride his favourite roller coaster. S3 Ep20</desc>
<end>0130</end>
<title>The Cleveland Show</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>For Whom The Booty Calls</subtitle>
<start>0130</start>
<desc>US comedy series. Walden joins a group for adoptive fathers and finds it to be a nice escape from Alan. S12 Ep11</desc>
<title>Two and a Half Men</title>
<end>0155</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>A Beer-Battered Rip-Off</subtitle>
<start>0155</start>
<desc>US comedy series. When Alan breaks up with their social worker to get back together with Lyndsey, Walden worries that it might affect Louis's adoption. S12 Ep12</desc>
<end>0225</end>
<title>Two and a Half Men</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0305</end>
<title>CelebAbility</title>
<desc>Iain Stirling hosts the final show of the series as five pals take on Joe Swash, Maya Jama, Jonnie Peacock, David Morgan and Laura Norton in a series of hilarious challenges. S1 Ep6</desc>
<start>0225</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0305</start>
<desc>...World Records. Matt Edmondson guides us through some more Guinness World Records, including the fastest time to pull an aircraft and the most watermelons punched in one minute. S2 Ep5</desc>
<title>Totally Bonkers Guinness...</title>
<end>0320</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0320</start>
<desc>Text-based information service.</desc>
<end>0330</end>
<title>ITV2 Nightscreen</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Teleshopping</title>
<end>0700</end>
<desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
<start>0330</start>
  </programme>
</channel>
