<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- produced for the bleb.org TV system at Wed Apr  1 07:21:24 2020 -->
<channel id="cbbc" source="XMLTV" date="06/04/2020">
  <programme>
<end>0700</end>
<title>This is CBBC!</title>
<start>0600</start>
<desc>This is CBBC! Join the CBBC crew for all your favourite programmes. Tune into CBBC every day from 7.00am.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0700</start>
<desc>The Butler Did It. Animated adventures of a young aardvark. When Mr Crosswire gets a robot butler for Father's Day, Muffy fears Bailey may be replaced. [S]</desc>
<end>0715</end>
<title>Arthur</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0715</start>
<desc>Are We There Yeti. Animated series. When the gang go on an adventure in search of the Beanotown Yeti, Walter follows with plans of his own for the rare beast. [S]</desc>
<end>0725</end>
<title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>City Day. Gluko and Lennon love Townopolis so much they make a commercial about it. The ad attracts huge crowds that clog the town, forcing them to make more ads to try to deter the visitors. [S]</desc>
<start>0725</start>
<title>Little Big Awesome</title>
<end>0735</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0735</start>
<desc>Greb-Nefual E-neg! Boy is scared by a horror film that the others think is lame, until one by one the others disappear, leaving Boy to save them from the 'shadow realm'. [S]</desc>
<end>0750</end>
<title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>If a Man... Just when everyone is getting sick and tired of Mrs Hushman, everyone's favourite maths teacher returns. [S]</desc>
<start>0750</start>
<title>Class Dismissed</title>
<end>0805</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Grave New World. Reality-style drama series. As the new strict studio head of the Next Step is revealed, so is the fate of Michelle and Emily. [S]</desc>
<start>0805</start>
<title>The Next Step</title>
<end>0830</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0830</start>
<desc>Episode 1. Four junior bakers, Alyth, Harrison, Kiah and Matthew, have their baking knowledge tested when they're asked to follow a surprise recipe for strawberry shortcake stacks. [S]</desc>
<end>0900</end>
<title>Junior Bake Off</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Chocolate Party. The Crafters get creative to make incredible art and fantastic food ready for an amazing party, and you're all invited! [S]</desc>
<start>0900</start>
<title>Craft Party</title>
<end>0915</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0915</start>
<desc>06/04/2020. Topical news magazine for children. [S]</desc>
<end>0925</end>
<title>Newsround</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0925</start>
<desc>One-off family comedy. Dennis is an ordinary boy but he feels different. He creates a whole new persona and puts it to the ultimate test - can a boy wear a dress? [S,AD]</desc>
<end>1030</end>
<title>The Boy in the Dress</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Absolute Genius: Monster Builds</title>
<end>1100</end>
<desc>Battling Nature. Dick and Dom go head to head with the fiercest forces in nature as they enter the genius world of engineering against floods, wind and earthquakes. [S]</desc>
<start>1030</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1100</start>
<desc>Angry Animals. Tim and Naomi search the natural world for all things weird. This time featuring angry animals, including flying fish and a lemming terrorising a cat. [S]</desc>
<end>1115</end>
<title>Wild &amp; Weird</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1115</start>
<desc>St Oswald's v St Peter's. This quarter-final sees St Oswald's take on St Peter's. Who will make it through to the semi-finals? Susan Calman presents. [S]</desc>
<end>1140</end>
<title>Top Class</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1210</end>
<title>Millie Inbetween</title>
<start>1140</start>
<desc>Gloria. Comedy drama series. An unexpected visit from Great Aunt Gloria, Mum's harshest critic, means emergency plans are needed. [S]</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1210</start>
<desc>06/04/2020. Topical news magazine for children. [S]</desc>
<end>1215</end>
<title>Newsround</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Surprise, Surprise. Comedy drama series. It's Millie's 13th birthday and both her mum and dad want to throw a party for her, but Millie can't decide which party she'd rather have. [S]</desc>
<start>1215</start>
<title>Millie Inbetween</title>
<end>1245</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1245</start>
<desc>Take a Hike. Comedy drama series. Millie turns teen and has her first crush, while Craig gets a Saturday job and Lauren takes a hike. Will Mike pop the question? [S]</desc>
<end>1315</end>
<title>Millie Inbetween</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Gym Stars</title>
<end>1335</end>
<desc>Episode 1. Series following young gymnasts. The female Elite team head to Brussels to battle the best artistic gymnasts in Europe at the start of the season. [S]</desc>
<start>1315</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Gym Stars</title>
<end>1355</end>
<desc>Bouncing Back. Series following young gymnasts. The rhythmic team has a fight on their hands when a member quits and the team's reserve steps in. [S]</desc>
<start>1335</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1355</start>
<desc>Obsessions. The Lifebabble team tackle issues important to young people. The team talk about being a fan - how it's okay to look up to someone and when it can go a bit too far. [S]</desc>
<end>1400</end>
<title>Lifebabble</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Observatory Den. Mark and Lauren get the help of experts to design dream dens for children. Helena needs a den to help her reach for the stars and fulfil her science dreams. [S,SL]</desc>
<start>1400</start>
<title>The Dengineers</title>
<end>1430</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1455</end>
<title>Almost Never</title>
<start>1430</start>
<desc>Press Conference. GHF and The Wonderland's joint press conference for their tour doesn't go to plan once AJ gets involved, while Nate is distracted by his relationship status with Chloe. [S,SL]</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Pink Dawn. Animated series. Supervillain the Princess is determined to pinkify the world. Only Danger Mouse dressed as a little girl can save us. [S,AD]</desc>
<start>1455</start>
<title>Danger Mouse</title>
<end>1510</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1525</end>
<title>Diddy TV</title>
<start>1510</start>
<desc>Misty. Diddy Dick and Dom launch their own television channel. Programmes include Diddy Doctor Who, The Belch and top-rated game show Bees or No Bees. [S]</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1525</start>
<desc>Edubot 4000. Animated series. Fed up with Dennis pulling the wool over Mrs Creecher's eyes, Walter orchestrates a robot to take over Class 3C - with disastrous results! [S]</desc>
<end>1535</end>
<title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1550</end>
<title>Little Big Awesome</title>
<start>1535</start>
<desc>City Day. Gluko and Lennon love Townopolis so much they make a commercial about it. The ad attracts huge crowds that clog the town, forcing them to make more ads to try to deter the visitors. [S]</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Greb-Nefual E-neg! Boy is scared by a horror film that the others think is lame, until one by one the others disappear, leaving Boy to save them from the 'shadow realm'. [S]</desc>
<start>1550</start>
<title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
<end>1600</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Newsround</title>
<end>1605</end>
<desc>06/04/2020. Topical news magazine for children. [S]</desc>
<start>1600</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1615</end>
<title>Hey You What If?</title>
<start>1605</start>
<desc>You Fell Into a Black Hole? Experience the most extraordinary ride in the universe - falling into a black hole. [S]</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1615</start>
<desc>The World Turned Odd, Part Two. Oona, Olympia and Otis accidentally change the past, undoing every case they've ever solved. [S,AD]</desc>
<end>1640</end>
<title>Odd Squad: World Turned Odd Part 2</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>The Pets Factor</title>
<end>1700</end>
<desc>Maisey, Edna and Barry. Cat performs life-saving surgery on a poorly puss, James treats a sock-scoffing dog and Rory is given the runaround by a pair of mischievous ferrets. [S]</desc>
<start>1640</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Grounded. Mildred is horrified to find her magic is broken when visiting Izzy's farm. [S,AD]</desc>
<start>1700</start>
<title>New: The Worst Witch</title>
<end>1730</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1800</end>
<title>New: Malory Towers</title>
<start>1730</start>
<desc>The First Day. It's a fresh start for Darrell as she settles in for her first day at Malory Towers. [S,AD]</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>New: Deadly 60</title>
<end>1825</end>
<desc>Shark Rescue Special. Steve dives in the shark capital of the world, meets hammerhead and tiger sharks nose to nose and passionately explains why sharks need friends. [S]</desc>
<start>1800</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Shark Conservation. Steve Backshall shares tips for how we can help sharks, which are in danger because of overfishing and bycatch. [S]</desc>
<start>1825</start>
<title>Deadly 60: Our Planet Matters</title>
<end>1830</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1900</end>
<title>Operation Ouch!</title>
<start>1830</start>
<desc>It's a Tug-O-War! A tug of war in today's lab shows the incredible strength of your ligaments. [S]</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1900</start>
<desc>...Songs Special. Savage Songs Special. A special episode of the historical sketch show, featuring songs from the series by King Alfred, Henry VIII, William the Conqueror and more. [S,AD]</desc>
<end>1930</end>
<title>Horrible Histories: Savage...</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Shark Rescue Special. Steve dives with hammerhead and tiger sharks, exploring how to save them... [S] Followed by Deadly 60: Our Planet Matters; Steve Backshall explains why we should all love sharks.</desc>
<start>1930</start>
<title>Deadly 60</title>
<end>2000</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Millie Inbetween</title>
<end>2030</end>
<desc>Lauren Deleted. Comedy drama series. Lauren's social media usage is dangerously out of hand. With Millie's help she deletes herself, but craves what she's missing. [S]</desc>
<start>2000</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>2100</end>
<title>The Worst Witch</title>
<start>2030</start>
<desc>Grounded. Mildred is horrified to find her magic is broken when visiting Izzy's farm. [S,AD]</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>This is CBBC!</title>
<end>0000</end>
<desc>This is CBBC! Join the CBBC crew for all your favourite programmes. Tune into CBBC every day from 7.00am.</desc>
<start>2100</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0000</start>
<desc>This is CBBC! Join the CBBC crew for all your favourite programmes. Tune into CBBC every day from 7.00am.</desc>
<end>0600</end>
<title>This is CBBC!</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0600</start>
<desc>This is CBBC! Join the CBBC crew for all your favourite programmes. Tune into CBBC every day from 7.00am.</desc>
<end>0700</end>
<title>This is CBBC!</title>
  </programme>
</channel>
