<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- produced for the bleb.org TV system at Wed Apr  1 07:19:13 2020 -->
<channel id="ch4" source="XMLTV" date="06/04/2020">
  <programme>
<end>0630</end>
<title>Countdown</title>
<start>0550</start>
<desc>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Richard Madeley joins Susie Dent in Dictionary Corner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0655</end>
<title>Cheers</title>
<start>0630</start>
<subtitle>The Mail Goes to Jail</subtitle>
<desc>Norm helps out Cliff by delivering the mail when his friend is unwell, but then he's accused of tampering with the post and arrested. (S3 Ep17/25)</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0655</start>
<subtitle>Bar Bet</subtitle>
<desc>An absurd bet that Sam made during his wild days comes back to haunt him when the man he made the wager with shows up. If Sam can't triumph, he must forfeit the bar. (S3 Ep18/25)</desc>
<end>0720</end>
<title>Cheers</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0720</start>
<desc>Doug attends his high school reunion, hoping to relive the 'good old days', but gets more than he bargained for after getting together with an old friend.</desc>
<subtitle>Mild Bunch</subtitle>
<end>0745</end>
<title>The King of Queens</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0810</end>
<title>The King of Queens</title>
<start>0745</start>
<subtitle>Manhattan Project</subtitle>
<desc>A flat in Manhattan that Doug and Carrie wanted when they got married becomes available. Carrie expresses an interest in moving there, but Doug's not so sure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0810</start>
<subtitle>Left Back</subtitle>
<desc>Ray worries that he has passed on 'stupid' genes to Michael because his son may be held back a year at school, just as Ray was.</desc>
<end>0840</end>
<title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0910</end>
<title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
<start>0840</start>
<desc>Ray thinks a family portrait would make a great Christmas present for his parents, until Marie and Debra clash over who counts as 'family'.</desc>
<subtitle>The Christmas Picture</subtitle>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0910</start>
<subtitle>First Date</subtitle>
<desc>Niles organises a fake 'first date' for himself with a neighbour so that Daphne won't realise that she is the one he has romantic feelings for.</desc>
<end>0940</end>
<title>Frasier</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0940</start>
<desc>Roz meets the parents of her baby's father and is shocked to discover a family facial characteristic that simply can't be ignored.</desc>
<subtitle>Roz and the Schnoz</subtitle>
<end>1005</end>
<title>Frasier</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</title>
<end>1100</end>
<desc>Gordon Ramsay travels to Philadelphia to visit floundering Mexican restaurant Zocalo, which has become an albatross around the necks of its owners, married couple Greg and Mary Russell.</desc>
<start>1005</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Come Dine with Me</title>
<end>1200</end>
<desc>In Bristol, Nick has a problem with his chocolate-covered balls. Martin's food comes with a side order of terrible jokes. Laura serves vegan. And Tina provides an impromptu pom-pom lesson.</desc>
<start>1100</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1200</start>
<desc>Steph McGovern presents the brand-new daily programme live from her living room, featuring special guests and the latest information to help us navigate these unique times we are living in.</desc>
<end>1305</end>
<title>Live: The Steph Show</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Posh Pawnbrokers</title>
<end>1410</end>
<desc>In Sheffield, Dan hopes to clean up with Kim Woodburn's jewellery, and considers a deal on a £50,000 F1 car. In Kent, brothers Charlie and Patrick value 19 pictures by artist Darell Koons.</desc>
<start>1305</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Al Murray joins Susie Dent in Dictionary Corner.</desc>
<start>1410</start>
<title>Countdown</title>
<end>1500</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>A Place in the Sun</title>
<end>1600</end>
<desc>Poppy and John want to enjoy their retirement in the Lot-et-Garonne region of France. Can Ben Hillman find them the perfect place for their £175,000 budget?</desc>
<start>1500</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Escape to the Chateau: DIY</title>
<end>1700</end>
<desc>Mariam and Johnno create a French parterre garden, Phillip and his wife Janet move into Chateau de la Fare, and Emma and Paul renovate a Charles Rennie Mackintosh-inspired room. (S4 Ep11)</desc>
<start>1600</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1700</start>
<desc>The first visit of the week is to Bowlees Farm Holiday Cottages in County Durham, run by Tony and Viv Smith. Their guests love the views and facilities, but will they pay for their stay?</desc>
<end>1730</end>
<title>Four in a Bed</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>The first host in the Midlands, dog-lover Becci, hopes to be crowned top dog as she serves posh Cornish food, accompanied by curious canine conversations.</desc>
<start>1730</start>
<title>Come Dine with Me</title>
<end>1800</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1800</start>
<desc>Mr Burns loses all his money and employs Lisa to help him earn back his fortune. But they don't see eye to eye over ethical issues.</desc>
<subtitle>The Old Man and the Lisa</subtitle>
<end>1830</end>
<title>The Simpsons</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Hollyoaks</title>
<end>1900</end>
<desc>Felix blackmails Walter in order to get closer to Mitchell. There could be light at the end of the tunnel for Sienna. And Brody has a decision to make.</desc>
<start>1830</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Channel 4 News</title>
<end>2030</end>
<desc>Channel 4's flagship news programme. Including the weather.</desc>
<start>1900</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>2030</start>
<desc>Jamie Oliver shows the nation some incredible recipes, tips and hacks, tailored for the unique times we're living in, including beef and oxtail stew and pizza. (Ep4)</desc>
<end>2100</end>
<title>Jamie: Keep Cooking and Carry On</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>...Coronavirus</subtitle>
<desc>How does the UK function under the shadow of the coronavirus? This film, shot over 24 hours, touches on the funny and the poignant, and gauges the impact of CV19 on the UK.</desc>
<start>2100</start>
<title>New: A Day in the Life of...</title>
<end>2200</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>2200</start>
<desc>Putin returns to power under a storm after a four-year absence. His attempts to improve his popularity are hobbled by accusations of corruption. (Ep3/3)</desc>
<end>2300</end>
<title>New: Putin: A Russian Spy Story</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>A freak car accident in Cumbria leaves Richard fighting for his life. In Hampshire, horse rider Pat takes a nasty fall when her animal is spooked. (S3 Ep2)</desc>
<start>2300</start>
<title>Emergency Helicopter Medics</title>
<end>0005</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0005</start>
<desc>Gordon Ramsay visits Sam's Mediterranean Kabob Room in Monrovia, California, where he tries to mend relationships between the restaurant's owner, his wife and their children.</desc>
<end>0055</end>
<title>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0055</start>
<desc>For 20 years, Channel 4 has followed the lives of five children born with disabilities. They are now young adults tackling the reality of independence. But not everyone is coping. (S10 Ep2)</desc>
<end>0150</end>
<title>Born to Be Different</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0245</end>
<title>Couples Come Dine with Me</title>
<start>0150</start>
<desc>In the Lake District, first hosts Paul and Glenda welcome self-confessed gadget geek David and his partner Jane, and outdoorsy twenty-somethings Matt and Polly, to their static caravan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0340</end>
<title>The Supervet</title>
<start>0245</start>
<desc>Marley the dog is admitted to the clinic with severe dysplasia of the elbow. A Rhodesian ridgeback has a high-risk operation. And Noel treats an old gym buddy's injured pooch. (S9 Ep2/11)</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0435</end>
<title>Grand Designs Australia</title>
<start>0340</start>
<desc>Two Anglican reverends build a barn-inspired medieval manor with a spectacular two-storey Gothic window as its centrepiece in the Adelaide suburb of Hillbank. (S7 Ep4)</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Location, Location, Location</title>
<end>0530</end>
<desc>Kirstie Allsopp is in Barry in Wales to help a couple feeling bruised and battered by the property market, and Phil Spencer joins Will and Aby's search for a country home in the Wye Valley.</desc>
<start>0435</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Kirstie Allsopp learns paper sculpture, decoupage and paper embroidery for greeting cards, and feels she has found her calling. But will the judges at the Royal Wales Show agree?</desc>
<start>0530</start>
<title>Kirstie's Handmade Treasures</title>
<end>0550</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Countdown</title>
<end>0630</end>
<desc>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Richard Madeley joins Susie Dent in Dictionary Corner.</desc>
<start>0550</start>
  </programme>
</channel>
