<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- produced for the bleb.org TV system at Wed Apr  1 07:21:57 2020 -->
<channel id="e4" source="XMLTV" date="06/04/2020">
  <programme>
<start>0600</start>
<desc>Felix blackmails Walter in order to get closer to Mitchell. There could be light at the end of the tunnel for Sienna. And Brody has a decision to make.</desc>
<end>0630</end>
<title>Hollyoaks</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Scott is surprised when Walter asks him for help. Liberty wonders where her future lies. Sid is looking forward to some alone time with Juliet, but she has other ideas...</desc>
<start>0630</start>
<title>Hollyoaks</title>
<end>0700</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0700</start>
<subtitle>False Positive</subtitle>
<desc>There's chaos at Christmas when Marshall and Lily have a positive result on a pregnancy test, Robin chooses between two jobs, and Barney wants a diamond suit. (S6 Ep12/24)</desc>
<end>0730</end>
<title>How I Met Your Mother</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0800</end>
<title>How I Met Your Mother</title>
<start>0730</start>
<subtitle>Last Words</subtitle>
<desc>It's the day of Marshall's father's funeral. Marshall is upset when he remembers that the last piece of advice his dad gave him was to watch Crocodile Dundee III. (S6 Ep14/24)</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>First episode of the popular US sitcom about a politician and the man she employs to help look after her niece and nephew when they are suddenly left in her care. (S1 Ep1/30)</desc>
<subtitle>Pilot</subtitle>
<start>0800</start>
<title>Melissa &amp; Joey</title>
<end>0830</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0900</end>
<title>Melissa &amp; Joey</title>
<start>0830</start>
<desc>Mel dates a guy with ulterior motives. Joe deals with getting his stuff back from his ex-wife, while Lennox tries to make friends at her new school. (S1 Ep2/30)</desc>
<subtitle>Moving On</subtitle>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Mike &amp; Molly</title>
<end>0930</end>
<subtitle>Mike &amp; Molly's Excellent Adventure</subtitle>
<desc>Molly encourages Mike to embrace anything he wants in life. They try new things together, but reality sets in when it's time to pay the bill. (S4 Ep8)</desc>
<start>0900</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0930</start>
<desc>Following a dramatic argument with Joyce over money, Mike and Molly make a hasty decision to move into Mike's childhood bedroom at Peggy's house. (S4 Ep9)</desc>
<subtitle>Weekend at Peggy's</subtitle>
<end>1000</end>
<title>Mike &amp; Molly</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Sheldon and Raj go to a university party, where Raj lusts after a girl called Abby. Leonard regrets telling Penny he disapproves of her belief in psychics. (S3 Ep12/23)</desc>
<subtitle>The Psychic Vortex</subtitle>
<start>1000</start>
<title>The Big Bang Theory</title>
<end>1030</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1100</end>
<title>The Big Bang Theory</title>
<start>1030</start>
<subtitle>The Bozeman Reaction</subtitle>
<desc>Leonard and Sheldon's flat is burgled. Determined to outwit any thieves, the gang create a new state-of-the-art security system to protect the place. (S3 Ep13/23)</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>The Goldbergs</title>
<end>1130</end>
<desc>Murray and Geoff try to pull Beverly, Barry and Erica out of their shared misery after Lainey's departure. Coach Nick returns to town. (S6 Ep12)</desc>
<subtitle>The Pina Colada Episode</subtitle>
<start>1100</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>The Goldbergs</title>
<end>1200</end>
<desc>Beverly decides the street where the family lives needs another stop sign, and Barry realises he's neglected his college applications. (S6 Ep13)</desc>
<subtitle>I Coulda Been a Lawyer</subtitle>
<start>1130</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1200</start>
<subtitle>Bureau</subtitle>
<desc>Pimento's life is still in peril, so Captain Holt calls on an old friend in the FBI to help identify the crooked agent who tried to have him killed. (S3 Ep22/23)</desc>
<end>1230</end>
<title>Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1230</start>
<subtitle>Greg and Larry</subtitle>
<desc>The squad drop everything to intervene when they realise that Holt is in danger as the search for Pimento's hitman takes an unexpected turn. (S3 Ep23/23)</desc>
<end>1300</end>
<title>Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>The Convention Conundrum</subtitle>
<desc>After the guys miss out on Comic-Con tickets, Sheldon decides to hold his own comic book convention. The girls take tea at an upmarket hotel. (S7 Ep14/24)</desc>
<start>1300</start>
<title>The Big Bang Theory</title>
<end>1330</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Love is in the air when Amy manages to convince Sheldon to join her for a romantic train trip to Napa Valley to celebrate Valentine's Day. (S7 Ep15/24)</desc>
<subtitle>The Locomotive Manipulation</subtitle>
<start>1330</start>
<title>The Big Bang Theory</title>
<end>1400</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1400</start>
<subtitle>A Fright in the Attic</subtitle>
<desc>Mel tries to get the kids excited about Halloween. Joe investigates noises coming from the attic, where he discovers Lewis hiding from the police. (S1 Ep11/30)</desc>
<end>1430</end>
<title>Melissa &amp; Joey</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1500</end>
<title>Melissa &amp; Joey</title>
<start>1430</start>
<desc>Joe decides to start his own online business giving financial tips to investors and he asks Mel for some advice to help get the enterprise off the ground. (S1 Ep12/30)</desc>
<subtitle>Joe Knows</subtitle>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1500</start>
<desc>Molly catches Carl coming out of Victoria's bedroom late at night, but she is uncertain about whether or not she should tell Mike about it. (S4 Ep18)</desc>
<subtitle>Sex, Lies and Helicopters</subtitle>
<end>1530</end>
<title>Mike &amp; Molly</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Mike &amp; Molly</title>
<end>1600</end>
<desc>Mike is worried about Peggy's health and asks her to see a doctor after she forgets to turn off her bath taps and the tub falls through the ceiling. (S4 Ep19)</desc>
<subtitle>This Old Peggy</subtitle>
<start>1530</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>The Goldbergs</title>
<end>1630</end>
<subtitle>Mom Trumps Willow</subtitle>
<desc>Adam decides to see the movie Willow instead of spending Mother's Day with Beverly. Barry tires of his status as the family's middle child. (S6 Ep22)</desc>
<start>1600</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1700</end>
<title>The Goldbergs</title>
<start>1630</start>
<subtitle>Breakin'</subtitle>
<desc>Adam reveals that Barry never completed his community service requirement. Erica plans for her and Geoff to follow The Grateful Dead all summer. (S6 Ep23/23)</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1730</end>
<title>Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
<start>1700</start>
<subtitle>The Overmining</subtitle>
<desc>Peralta and Holt help CJ with a big case that is proving problematic. Jeffords tells Gina to remove her precious portable heater from the office. (S4 Ep9/22)</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1730</start>
<subtitle>Captain Latvia</subtitle>
<desc>Boyle enlists Peralta's help in tracking down his son's favourite toy for Christmas. The team face their rivals in the annual carol competition. (S4 Ep10/22)</desc>
<end>1800</end>
<title>Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1800</start>
<desc>With potential changes affecting different aspects of his personal and professional life, Sheldon is forced to confront an uncertain future. (S7 Ep24/24)</desc>
<subtitle>The Status Quo Combustion</subtitle>
<end>1830</end>
<title>The Big Bang Theory</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1830</start>
<desc>Leonard and Amy take an impromptu road trip to Arizona to pick up Sheldon when his epic railway journey ends in chaos. Penny has an interview. (S8 Ep1/24)</desc>
<subtitle>The Locomotion Interruption</subtitle>
<end>1900</end>
<title>The Big Bang Theory</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1930</end>
<title>Hollyoaks</title>
<start>1900</start>
<desc>Scott is surprised when Walter asks him for help. Liberty wonders where her future lies. Sid is looking forward to some alone time with Juliet, but she has other ideas...</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>New: Man with a Plan</title>
<end>2000</end>
<desc>Brand new series - March Madness: When Adam and Andi lose footage of an intimate moment they accidentally recorded, they have to track it down before anyone can see it. (S2 Ep14)</desc>
<start>1930</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>2100</end>
<title>New: First Dates Abroad</title>
<start>2000</start>
<desc>Brand new series: In Australia, electrician Brad meets Instagram model Sarah. And pole-dancing stockbroker Libby has a date with personal trainer Nick. (S7 Ep2)</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>New: Made in Chelsea</title>
<end>2200</end>
<desc>Brand new series: Jamie is furious with Emily for her disloyalty towards Habbs. Sam meets the parents. Verity and Tristan hit their first bump in the road: will it be their last? (S19 Ep3)</desc>
<start>2100</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>2305</end>
<title>New: The Sex Clinic</title>
<start>2200</start>
<desc>Brand new series: Sharif wants more confidence in the bedroom, Luke wants advice on safe sex during threesomes, Kamen needs an STI test, and Monique wants to discuss sex. (S2 Ep7)</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>The Proton Transmogrification</subtitle>
<desc>Sheldon struggles to process his feelings of grief when his idol Professor Proton passes away. The gang gather to celebrate Star Wars Day. (S7 Ep22/24)</desc>
<start>2305</start>
<title>The Big Bang Theory</title>
<end>2335</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>The Gorilla Dissolution</subtitle>
<desc>Penny re-evaluates her life, including taking a big step with Leonard, while Howard and Bernadette struggle to look after Mrs Wolowitz. (S7 Ep23/24)</desc>
<start>2335</start>
<title>The Big Bang Theory</title>
<end>0000</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Made in Chelsea</title>
<end>0105</end>
<desc>Brand new series: Jamie is furious with Emily for her disloyalty towards Habbs. Sam meets the parents. Verity and Tristan hit their first bump in the road: will it be their last? (S19 Ep3)</desc>
<start>0000</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0105</start>
<desc>What do Britain's sharpest viewers think of programmes including The Dirt, Catchpoint, Race Across the World, This Morning, and Married at First Sight? (S13 Ep6) [SL]</desc>
<end>0210</end>
<title>Gogglebox</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>First Dates Abroad</title>
<end>0305</end>
<desc>Brand new series: In Australia, electrician Brad meets Instagram model Sarah. And pole-dancing stockbroker Libby has a date with personal trainer Nick. (S7 Ep2)</desc>
<start>0210</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0305</start>
<desc>Brand new series: Sharif wants more confidence in the bedroom, Luke wants advice on safe sex during threesomes, Kamen needs an STI test, and Monique wants to discuss sex. (S2 Ep7)</desc>
<end>0400</end>
<title>The Sex Clinic</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0400</start>
<desc>Sheldon and Raj go to a university party, where Raj lusts after a girl called Abby. Leonard regrets telling Penny he disapproves of her belief in psychics. (S3 Ep12/23)</desc>
<subtitle>The Psychic Vortex</subtitle>
<end>0425</end>
<title>The Big Bang Theory</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0450</end>
<title>The Big Bang Theory</title>
<start>0425</start>
<subtitle>The Bozeman Reaction</subtitle>
<desc>Leonard and Sheldon's flat is burgled. Determined to outwit any thieves, the gang create a new state-of-the-art security system to protect the place. (S3 Ep13/23)</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0450</start>
<subtitle>False Positive</subtitle>
<desc>There's chaos at Christmas when Marshall and Lily have a positive result on a pregnancy test, Robin chooses between two jobs, and Barney wants a diamond suit. (S6 Ep12/24)</desc>
<end>0515</end>
<title>How I Met Your Mother</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0600</end>
<title>How I Met Your Mother</title>
<start>0515</start>
<desc>It's the day of Marshall's father's funeral. Marshall is upset when he remembers that the last piece of advice his dad gave him was to watch Crocodile Dundee III. (S6 Ep14/24)</desc>
<subtitle>Last Words</subtitle>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Hollyoaks</title>
<end>0630</end>
<desc>Sienna is convinced something is going to go terribly wrong, and Liberty is determined to sort things out. Felix has an idea to win over Mitchell, and Juliet blows hot and cold with Sid.</desc>
<start>0600</start>
  </programme>
</channel>
