<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- produced for the bleb.org TV system at Wed Apr  1 07:19:17 2020 -->
<channel id="five" source="XMLTV" date="06/04/2020">
  <programme>
<desc>Animation. Lee, Sioux and Mofy get lost in the wood while they are looking for a rare nut tree, but Mofy's eye for details help them find the way back home. (S3 Ep 18)</desc>
<start>0600</start>
<title>Mofy</title>
<end>0605</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Peppa Pig</title>
<end>0610</end>
<subtitle>Basketball</subtitle>
<desc>Animated series about a loveable little pig. Daddy teaches the children how to play basketball, and it is not long before they are good enough to take on a team. (S4 Ep 3)</desc>
<start>0605</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0610</start>
<subtitle>Horsey Twinkle Toes</subtitle>
<desc>Animated series about a loveable little pig. There is much excitement when Mr Zebra delivers a package from Aunt Dottie for Peppa and George. (S4 Ep 4)</desc>
<end>0615</end>
<title>Peppa Pig</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Peppa Pig</title>
<end>0620</end>
<desc>Animated series about a loveable little pig. Dr Hamster's pet tortoise Tiddles gets stuck up a tree - who is going to come to the rescue? (S4 Ep 5)</desc>
<subtitle>Naughty Tortoise</subtitle>
<start>0615</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0620</start>
<subtitle>Pontypandy Heatwave</subtitle>
<desc>Fun with the friendly fireman and the villagers of Pontypandy. Fireman Sam is needed when two fires start during Joe and Trevor's barbecues. (S9 Ep 15)</desc>
<end>0630</end>
<title>Fireman Sam</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0645</end>
<title>Noddy Toyland Detective</title>
<start>0630</start>
<desc>Animated series based on Enid Blyton's character. Carlton is organising the Builders' Parade, but all the supplies in the Brickabuild Store are missing! (S2 Ep 42)</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Abby Hatcher</title>
<end>0655</end>
<desc>Animated series about a young girl and her quirky Fuzzly friends. Princess Flug thinks that Melvin's surprise party is for her and gets upset when it isn't. (S1 Ep 6)</desc>
<start>0645</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Thomas &amp; Friends: Big World!...</title>
<end>0710</end>
<desc>...Big Adventures! CGI animated escapades of the little blue engine. Bulgy thinks that people should travel by bus instead of rail - until he tries carrying all their passengers. (S23 Ep 1)</desc>
<start>0655</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0710</start>
<desc>2D animated series about two inquisitive four-year-olds. Herbie has a thorn stuck in his paw, so Daddy, Daisy and Ollie take him to Louise the vet. (S3 Ep 6)</desc>
<end>0720</end>
<title>New: Daisy &amp; Ollie</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Peppa Pig</title>
<end>0730</end>
<subtitle>George's Friend</subtitle>
<desc>Animated series about a lovable little pig. Rebecca Rabbit has a little brother called Richard who is the same age as George. (S2 Ep 6)</desc>
<start>0720</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Animated exploits of a lovable piglet. Peppa's family squeeze into 'The Electric Car' that Daddy Pig is trying out for fun. (S6 Ep 39)</desc>
<start>0730</start>
<title>Peppa Pig</title>
<end>0740</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Top Wing</title>
<end>0755</end>
<desc>Animated series about bird rescue-cadets. When Rod's beloved Rooster Brewster goes missing, the cadets must rescue the soft toy so that everyone can rest again. (S2 Ep 18)</desc>
<start>0740</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Animated series about a team of search-and-rescue pups. When an ancient relic goes missing, Tracker and Skye must track down the creature that may have taken it. (S5 Ep 6)</desc>
<start>0755</start>
<title>PAW Patrol</title>
<end>0810</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>New: Floogals</title>
<end>0825</end>
<desc>Animated series about three tiny aliens exploring our world. When Boomer realises the Hoomans are out of raisins, the Floogals venture into a grocery shop. (S3 Ep 21)</desc>
<start>0810</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Secret Life Of Puppies</title>
<end>0835</end>
<desc>A dog's-eye view of life. Meet Barley, a Newfoundland puppy with a big personality. We join her as she learns to listen and play gently with her mum Willow. (S2 Ep 1)</desc>
<start>0825</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Milkshake! Monkey's...</title>
<end>0845</end>
<desc>...Amazing Adventures. Live action series featuring an inquisitive puppet monkey. Milkshake! Monkey visits the Met Office to find out where rain comes from. Clare tells him about the water cycle.</desc>
<start>0835</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0845</start>
<desc>2D-animated series about a little girl who lives in a castle. Princess wants to wake up every day with something pretty to look at next to her bed. (S7 Ep 3)</desc>
<end>0855</end>
<title>Little Princess</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0910</end>
<title>Ben and Holly's Little Kingdom</title>
<start>0855</start>
<desc>Animation. The Little Kingdom and all of the dads are given the day off work to go and play together in the meadow. (S2 Ep 45)</desc>
<subtitle>Fathers Day</subtitle>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>New: Sunny Bunnies</title>
<end>0915</end>
<desc>Animated exploits of five colourful balls of light. When a seesaw mishap strands Shiny on top of a castle tower, she needs rescuing just like a medieval princess. (S4 Ep 1)</desc>
<start>0910</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1120</end>
<title>Jeremy Vine</title>
<start>0915</start>
<desc>Jeremy Vine discusses and dissects the latest news, views and opinions, with co-host Storm Huntley helping on the live phone-ins.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Documentary series. Emmanuel reveals what happened after he returned from working abroad to find himself 24,000 in mortgage arrears and unable to get into his own home. (S4 Ep 7)</desc>
<start>1120</start>
<title>Bad Tenants, Rogue Landlords</title>
<end>1210</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>5 News At Lunchtime</title>
<end>1215</end>
<desc>National and international news.</desc>
<start>1210</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1215</start>
<desc>Documentary series. Meet Mark aka popular drag act Ruby Rox, two caravanners on a tiny budget, two tattooists who set up a parlour, and a woman who teaches Spanish to the Brits. (S2 Ep 5)</desc>
<end>1310</end>
<title>Bargain-Loving Brits in The Sun</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1315</end>
<title>Access</title>
<start>1310</start>
<desc>A daily round-up of showbiz news and gossip from around the world, focusing on celebrities, movies, music and entertainment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1315</start>
<desc>Dean invites Ziggy to move in with him without consulting Colby. Bella starts to admit she needs counselling. Alex realises how much Jasmine is depending on Willow for support.</desc>
<end>1345</end>
<title>Home and Away</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1415</end>
<title>Neighbours</title>
<start>1345</start>
<desc>Finn's video diaries have unexpected consequences. Ramsay Street rallies to help Kyle as he returns to work. Mackenzie needs to consult the Rebecchis over a secret dilemma.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Thriller starring Haley Webb and Donny Boaz. A woman being terrorized by a stalker hires and develops a relationship with a mysterious private detective. (2018)</desc>
<start>1415</start>
<title>Serial Killer Cove</title>
<end>1600</end>
<type>Film</type>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Friends</title>
<end>1630</end>
<desc>Rachel submits to peer pressure at work. Joey auditions against Ross's son. Monica and Phoebe plan a surprise birthday party for Rachel. (S5 Ep 18)</desc>
<start>1600</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1630</start>
<desc>Ross's flirting technique fails to impress. Joey is in for a surprise when he tells everyone about his big television appearance. (S5 Ep 19)</desc>
<end>1700</end>
<title>Friends</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>National and international news.</desc>
<start>1700</start>
<title>5 News At 5</title>
<end>1730</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1800</end>
<title>Neighbours</title>
<start>1730</start>
<desc>Finn's video diaries have unexpected consequences. Ramsay Street rallies to help Kyle as he returns to work. Mackenzie needs to consult the Rebecchis over a secret dilemma.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Entertainment round up.</desc>
<start>1800</start>
<title>Access</title>
<end>1810</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>The Yorkshire Steam Railway:..</title>
<end>1900</end>
<desc>...All Aboard. Documentary series going behind the scenes of the North Yorkshire Moors Railway. A summer heatwave brings record numbers to the railway, but also risks fires. (S2 Ep 1)</desc>
<start>1810</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1900</start>
<desc>...Tony Robinson. Tony takes a less-well trodden train trip around the globe. Tony's rides the rails through the heart of South America, as he explores Argentina and Peru. (S2 Ep 2)</desc>
<end>2000</end>
<title>Around the World by Train with...</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Reality series following high-speed police intercept units in West Yorkshire. A driver rams into Bob three times in reverse before speeding down an off-road track. (S17 Ep 11)</desc>
<start>2000</start>
<title>New: Police Interceptors</title>
<end>2100</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>New: Inside the Force: 24/7</title>
<end>2200</end>
<desc>The reality of life inside a busy police station. PC Jess and PC Simon are involved in urgent manhunts across Lincoln. A suspect is wanted for sexual assault as well as stalking. (S1 Ep 3)</desc>
<start>2100</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>New: Hard Men: Street Justice</title>
<end>2300</end>
<desc>Inside some of the country's most notorious gangs. The rivalry between Manchester's Gooch Gang and the Doddington Gang has been likened to the deadly gang wars of LA. (S1 Ep 2)</desc>
<start>2200</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Gangland drama starring Simon Cotton and Kevin Leslie. Criminal twins Ronnie and Reggie Kray lay the foundations for a brutal and unforgiving crime empire. (2015)</desc>
<start>2300</start>
<title>Rise of the Krays</title>
<type>Film</type>
<end>0115</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0315</end>
<title>The 21.co.uk Live Casino Show</title>
<start>0115</start>
<desc>Interactive casino show featuring live roulette. For more information and to register, visit www.21.co.uk.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0315</start>
<desc>Documentary series filmed inside Hall Green Health Centre in Birmingham. When Zenub comes in with an eye irritation there are many possible diagnoses. (S7 Ep 3)</desc>
<end>0405</end>
<title>GPs Behind Closed Doors</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Glamorous gran Amanda loves to compare herself to her granddaughter and isn't afraid to grow old disgracefully. [SL] (S1 Ep 1)</desc>
<start>0405</start>
<title>My Mum's Hotter Than Me!</title>
<end>0455</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0455</start>
<desc>US interior designer Ann Maurice lays down the law to those whose houses need updating to make a sale. Will she succeed in prescribing what they need? [SL] (S2 Ep 7)</desc>
<end>0520</end>
<title>House Doctor</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Great Artists</title>
<end>0550</end>
<desc>Tim Marlow looks at the work of some of the Western world's most famous artists. The Venetian Tiziano Vecellio pioneered the use of oils with a radical approach. (S1 Ep 6)</desc>
<start>0520</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Entertainment round up.</desc>
<start>0550</start>
<title>Access</title>
<end>0600</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0605</end>
<title>Mofy</title>
<start>0600</start>
<desc>Animation. Thanks to Mogu's tales, Mofy learns that it is not necessary for something to be new for her to appreciate it. (S3 Ep 19)</desc>
  </programme>
</channel>
