<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- produced for the bleb.org TV system at Tue Mar 31 09:45:06 2020 -->
<channel id="p_itv2" source="XMLTV" date="06/04/2020">
  <programme>
<title>Teleshopping</title>
<end>0700</end>
<desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
<start>0330</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>The Ellen DeGeneres Show</title>
<start>0700</start>
<desc>Ellen is joined by America's Got Talent judge Simon Cowell and the contestant who became the first winner of American Ninja Warrior in four years. S17 Ep7</desc>
<end>0750</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Emmerdale</title>
<start>0750</start>
<desc>Will steals off Cain. Jai interrupts Priya and Al. Bob comes up with a plan.</desc>
<end>0820</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0820</start>
<desc>Yasmeen confronts Geoff with the contents of his emails. Gemma tries to be positive as Aled's hearing aid is fitted. David apologises for using Alina.</desc>
<end>0850</end>
<title>Coronation Street</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Narrated by Harry Hill. Including the illicit craze of face-changing that renders photo IDs useless, and a video so terrible it will stay in your mind forever. S26 Ep2</desc>
<end>0920</end>
<start>0850</start>
<title>You've Been Framed! Gold</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Part-Time Hires</subtitle>
<start>0920</start>
<end>0950</end>
<desc>Amy struggles with parenting conflicts when her daughter joins the staff. Garrett and Dina disagree over how their relationship ended. S3 Ep3</desc>
<title>Superstore</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Superstore</title>
<subtitle>Workplace Bullying</subtitle>
<start>0950</start>
<end>1015</end>
<desc>An attempted robbery causes a headache for the store employees, with Dina facing off against Jonah. Glenn is given the task of firing the security guard. S3 Ep4</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Dinner Date</title>
<subtitle>Daisy</subtitle>
<start>1015</start>
<end>1115</end>
<desc>Culinary-themed dating series. Daisy from London chooses three dates based on the mouth-watering menus they have put together. Who will she want to see again? S7 Ep24</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Dress To Impress</title>
<subtitle>Aaron</subtitle>
<start>1115</start>
<desc>Dating series with a difference. Three singletons hope to win a date with professional street dancer Aaron by each buying him an outfit. S1 Ep2</desc>
<end>1215</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1245</end>
<desc>Will steals off Cain. Jai interrupts Priya and Al. Bob comes up with a plan.</desc>
<start>1215</start>
<title>Emmerdale</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1245</start>
<end>1320</end>
<desc>Yasmeen confronts Geoff with the contents of his emails. Gemma tries to be positive as Aled's hearing aid is fitted. David apologises for using Alina.</desc>
<title>Coronation Street</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>You've Been Framed! Gold</title>
<start>1320</start>
<desc>Surreal comedy as Harry Hill narrates more videos. Abi Titmuss tugs on a lemur, while Nadine Dorries puts the dry skin off her scalp to good use. S26 Ep3</desc>
<end>1350</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1350</start>
<desc>The host is joined by Renee Zellweger, who discusses starring as Judy Garland in new film Judy. Plus, Katy Perry chats to Ellen before performing her latest hit, Small Talk. S17 Ep8</desc>
<end>1445</end>
<title>The Ellen DeGeneres Show</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Matt</subtitle>
<start>1445</start>
<desc>Culinary-themed dating series. Matt from Somerset chooses three dates based on five menus. When the dinners have been eaten, who will he want to see for seconds? S7 Ep25</desc>
<end>1550</end>
<title>Dinner Date</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Lily</subtitle>
<start>1550</start>
<end>1650</end>
<desc>Dating series with a difference. Three singletons try to impress cheerleader Lily Amelia with their choice of outfit from Leeds town centre. S1 Ep5</desc>
<title>Dress To Impress</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Take Me Out</title>
<start>1650</start>
<end>1800</end>
<desc>In the love lift are personal trainer and computer geek Marcus, airline pilot Ross, musician and magician Rad and city banker Stephen. S11 Ep4</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>You've Been Framed! Gold</title>
<start>1800</start>
<desc>Harry Hill narrates more wacky videos. Dogs reveal where they stand on Europe, while Harry plots to spread verrucas across the UK. S26 Ep9</desc>
<end>1830</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1830</start>
<desc>Harry Hill skewers the world's funniest home videos. A tiny archaeologist digs up more than anyone bargained for, and an eating competition unveils the answer to childhood obesity. S26 Ep10</desc>
<end>1900</end>
<title>You've Been Framed! Gold</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1900</start>
<desc>Harry Hill narrates more videos. Featuring a toddler who destroys Stonehenge, babysitting tips from a cross-dressing dad, and the world's first heavy-petting zoo. S26 Ep11</desc>
<end>1930</end>
<title>You've Been Framed! Gold</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Harry Hill narrates more viewers' home videos, featuring odd mating rituals in Cornwall and a cat who refuses to be put down. Harry also discovers an illegitimate son. S26 Ep12</desc>
<end>2000</end>
<start>1930</start>
<title>You've Been Framed! Gold</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>US comedy series. Alan and Walden befriend three mums at a kids' gym, but things get complicated when Walden becomes attracted to one of them. S12 Ep7</desc>
<end>2030</end>
<start>2000</start>
<subtitle>Sex with an Animated Ed Asner</subtitle>
<title>Two and a Half Men</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Two and a Half Men</title>
<desc>US comedy series. Walden and Alan are determined to convince Louis that Santa Claus is real. Meanwhile, Walden's stalker Rose returns. S12 Ep8</desc>
<end>2100</end>
<start>2030</start>
<subtitle>Family, Bublé, Deep-Fried Turkey</subtitle>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>New: Family Guy</title>
<end>2130</end>
<desc>Peter is grounded by Lois after secretly overspending the family money on a credit card. Planning a perfect escape, he builds a tunnel directly to the pub. S18 Ep12</desc>
<start>2100</start>
<subtitle>Undergrounded</subtitle>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Steve leaves to go to boarding school - unaware that is just for girls. Meanwhile, Stan is annoyed by the people who take Steve's place in the family home. S15 Ep6</desc>
<end>2200</end>
<start>2130</start>
<subtitle>Top of the Steve</subtitle>
<title>New: American Dad!</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Family Guy</title>
<end>2230</end>
<desc>Animated comedy. Peter and the guys set out to throw Jesus the best birthday party ever to help him lose his virginity. S13 Ep7</desc>
<start>2200</start>
<subtitle>The 2,000-Year-Old-Virgin</subtitle>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Family Guy</title>
<subtitle>The Most Interesting Man in the World</subtitle>
<start>2230</start>
<desc>US animated comedy. After being told by Lois how stupid he is, Peter accepts more business trips away and soon becomes clever and cultured. S12 Ep17</desc>
<end>2255</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Family Guy</title>
<desc>US animated comedy. Chris and Jerome's daughter Pam run away together when Jerome forbids them from seeing each other. S12 Ep18</desc>
<end>2325</end>
<start>2255</start>
<subtitle>Baby Got Black</subtitle>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Ciapow</subtitle>
<start>2325</start>
<end>2355</end>
<desc>Animated comedy. Stan and his CIA co-workers go to Thailand to blow up a weapons cache, but Bullock has already sent a drone to do the job. S11 Ep5</desc>
<title>American Dad!</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>After he is given a makeover, Cleveland Jr finally gains enough self-confidence to start talking to girls. S3 Ep22</desc>
<end>0025</end>
<start>2355</start>
<subtitle>All You Can Eat</subtitle>
<title>The Cleveland Show</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Escape from Goochland</subtitle>
<start>0025</start>
<end>0050</end>
<desc>Animated spin-off from Family Guy. Cleveland and his friends visit Goochland for the annual football game against their high-school rivals. S4 Ep1</desc>
<title>The Cleveland Show</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Two and a Half Men</title>
<subtitle>Sex with an Animated Ed Asner</subtitle>
<start>0050</start>
<desc>US comedy series. Alan and Walden befriend three mums at a kids' gym, but things get complicated when Walden becomes attracted to one of them. S12 Ep7</desc>
<end>0120</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Two and a Half Men</title>
<end>0150</end>
<desc>US comedy series. Walden and Alan are determined to convince Louis that Santa Claus is real. Meanwhile, Walden's stalker Rose returns. S12 Ep8</desc>
<start>0120</start>
<subtitle>Family, Bublé, Deep-Fried Turkey</subtitle>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>The boys gate-crash a posh banquet, where Marcus tries to win favour with the host, Jason seduces a bored aristocrat and Grumio overhears a poison plot. S5 Ep3</desc>
<end>0220</end>
<start>0150</start>
<subtitle>The Banquet</subtitle>
<title>Plebs</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Plebs</title>
<desc>There's a heatwave in Rome and Marcus has invested in a new gimmick for the bar - ice. Plus, Grumio develops a hat-parasol hybrid, which attracts attention. S5 Ep4</desc>
<end>0250</end>
<start>0220</start>
<subtitle>The Grumbrella</subtitle>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0250</start>
<end>0315</end>
<desc>...World Records. Matt Edmondson looks at entertaining world records. Featuring a human cannonball and the record for the most meatballs eaten in one minute. S1 Ep3</desc>
<title>Totally Bonkers Guinness...</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>ITV2 Nightscreen</title>
<start>0315</start>
<desc>Text-based information service.</desc>
<end>0330</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Teleshopping</title>
<desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
<end>0700</end>
<start>0330</start>
  </programme>
</channel>
