<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- produced for the bleb.org TV system at Sat Apr  4 07:19:14 2020 -->
<channel id="ch4" source="XMLTV" date="09/04/2020">
  <programme>
<desc>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Al Murray joins Susie Dent in Dictionary Corner.</desc>
<start>0550</start>
<title>Countdown</title>
<end>0630</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Carla insists Sam should hire an older woman to replace Diane. She thinks she's found the perfect candidate in Lillian, whose daughter catches Sam's eye. (S3 Ep23/25)</desc>
<start>0630</start>
<subtitle>The Bartender's Tale</subtitle>
<title>Cheers</title>
<end>0655</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Carla calls together her former school classmates so they can plot revenge when she spots their sadistic former principal having a drink at Cheers. (S3 Ep24/25)</desc>
<start>0655</start>
<subtitle>The Belles of St Clete's</subtitle>
<title>Cheers</title>
<end>0720</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Fat City</subtitle>
<start>0720</start>
<desc>While browsing one of Arthur's photo albums, Doug sees a picture of Carrie's heavyset mother. Arthur's comment about all women in the family getting fat makes Doug panic.</desc>
<title>The King of Queens</title>
<end>0745</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0810</end>
<title>The King of Queens</title>
<desc>When Carrie tells Doug to ignore her 30th birthday, he is more than happy to play along, because there's a huge ultimate fighting tournament on TV.</desc>
<subtitle>Crappy Birthday</subtitle>
<start>0745</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Hackidu</subtitle>
<start>0810</start>
<desc>Ray shows an interest in Ally's 'Hackidu' trading card hobby, but inadvertently gives away her favourite 'Scramisaur' card.</desc>
<end>0840</end>
<title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Debra Makes Something Good</subtitle>
<start>0840</start>
<desc>Debra finally cooks a dish that Ray, Robert and Frank all enjoy, but Marie is not impressed with her efforts.</desc>
<end>0910</end>
<title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0940</end>
<title>Frasier</title>
<start>0910</start>
<subtitle>Frasier's Curse</subtitle>
<desc>Frasier worries about going to his high school reunion, because every time a reunion comes up he has bad luck.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Frasier</title>
<end>1005</end>
<desc>Frasier's unemployed status puts him on edge with everyone and, when he blows up at Martin, Roz suggests that Martin moves in with Niles.</desc>
<start>0940</start>
<subtitle>Dial M for Martin</subtitle>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</title>
<end>1100</end>
<desc>Gordon Ramsay travels to Baltimore, Maryland, to try to save the struggling Café Hon restaurant, which is suffering because its owner has alienated the surrounding community.</desc>
<start>1005</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>In Greater Manchester, the competition starts with a fiesta on David's Spanish evening. But when Sukie dishes up a menu from her native South Korea, is her authentic dessert a step too far?</desc>
<start>1100</start>
<title>Come Dine with Me</title>
<end>1200</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1305</end>
<title>Live: The Steph Show</title>
<desc>Steph McGovern presents the new daily programme live from her living room with the latest information to help us in these unique times we are living in and special guest Josh Widdicombe.</desc>
<start>1200</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1305</start>
<desc>In Sheffield, Dan and his team hope to do deals on a diamond eternity ring, a Victorian gold chain and some unusual painted cabinets featuring Salvador Dali. Plus: an Oasis gold disc.</desc>
<title>Posh Pawnbrokers</title>
<end>1410</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1410</start>
<desc>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Al Murray joins Susie Dent in Dictionary Corner.</desc>
<end>1500</end>
<title>Countdown</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1500</start>
<desc>Gerry and Kathy want to buy a holiday home on the coast, but can't agree on where it should be. Will it be the coastline of Pembrokeshire in Wales or the Greek island of Zakynthos?</desc>
<end>1600</end>
<title>A Place in the Sun: Home or Away</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Emma and Paul take on a massive garden project, Mariam and Johnno launch their chateau as an events venue, and Karen and Paul's roof renovation costs spiral out of control. (S4 Ep14)</desc>
<start>1600</start>
<end>1700</end>
<title>Escape to the Chateau: DIY</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1730</end>
<title>Four in a Bed</title>
<desc>The final visit of the week is to Evenlode Grounds in the Cotswolds, owned by Howard and Amanda Wooliams. Everyone is glad to be glamping, but the feedback leads to questions.</desc>
<start>1700</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1730</start>
<desc>...Carry On: Jamie Oliver shows us some incredible recipes, tips and hacks tailored for the unique times we're living in. (Ep14)</desc>
<title>New: Jamie: Keep Cooking and...</title>
<end>1800</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>The Simpsons</title>
<end>1830</end>
<subtitle>The Secret War of Lisa Simpson</subtitle>
<start>1800</start>
<desc>Bart and Lisa enrol in military school, but Lisa finds it hard to fit in. Guest starring Willem Dafoe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>The Simpsons</title>
<end>1900</end>
<desc>Homer is charged for fighting at the St Patrick's Day parade. He thinks becoming a bounty hunter will solve his problems, but he soon runs into more trouble.</desc>
<subtitle>Sex, Pies and Idiot Scrapes</subtitle>
<start>1830</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1900</start>
<desc>Channel 4's flagship news programme. Including the weather.</desc>
<title>Channel 4 News</title>
<end>2000</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>2000</start>
<desc>...Your House?: How does coronavirus work? How does it use our behaviour to get into our homes? And which products could stop it?</desc>
<end>2100</end>
<title>New: Coronavirus: How Clean Is...</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>2200</end>
<title>New: The Mum Who Got Tourette's</title>
<start>2100</start>
<desc>Elizabeth developed Tourette's when she was 40. This personal, fun and moving documentary provides an insight into how an ordinary family deals with an extraordinary condition.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Fine art student Michael expresses his emotions through his work, but there's one emotion he's yet to paint - love. And showgirl Zena is looking for someone to settle down with. (S11 Ep5)</desc>
<start>2200</start>
<title>New: The Undateables</title>
<end>2230</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>2230</start>
<desc>The restaurant throws open its doors to hopeful singletons. Jessica, who's 28, seeks a James Corden doppelganger, while Dottie, who's 71, goes on her first date in 51 years. (S13 Ep1)</desc>
<end>2330</end>
<title>First Dates</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>2330</start>
<desc>...Changing - Dispatches: Dispatches investigates how the coronavirus outbreak is changing Britain in the long term, for better or worse, and from a fall in pollution to economic policy.</desc>
<title>Coronavirus: How Britain Is...</title>
<end>0035</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0035</start>
<desc>Gordon is in Norwalk, Ohio, for the first of two visits to the Mill Street Bistro, where the owner claims he has the best menu between New York and LA, but the diners disagree.</desc>
<title>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</title>
<end>0125</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Feel Good</title>
<end>0150</end>
<desc>Comedy about love and addiction. Mae apologises to her parents for her past transgressions as an addict. But if she's expecting anything in return, she's going to have a long wait... (Ep4) [SL]</desc>
<start>0125</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0150</start>
<desc>For 33-year-old Nina, appearances are everything. She invites five potential suitors into her immaculate flat, as she looks for a guy who won't be out of place in her beloved des res. (Ep5)</desc>
<end>0245</end>
<title>Five Guys a Week</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0245</start>
<desc>Architect Tim Hill is upsizing from an award-winning but small home, known as The Lighthouse, to a curvaceous house shaped like a foot in Kensington in Melbourne. (S7 Ep6)</desc>
<end>0340</end>
<title>Grand Designs Australia</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>In Kent, Stephanie and Ian's home, a tiny version of the Palace of Versailles, amazes their guests. Is their food as impressive? Later in the week, there's dressing up and stripping off.</desc>
<start>0340</start>
<title>Couples Come Dine with Me</title>
<end>0435</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Phil Spencer catches up with Steve and Sally in Warwickshire. And Kirstie Allsopp revisits Rinku and Sunder in Northamptonshire, whose last home was up for demolition. What happened next?</desc>
<start>0435</start>
<end>0530</end>
<title>Location, Location, Location</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0530</start>
<desc>Kirstie Allsopp gets her bangers in a twist making sausages and pork pies for a competition at the Nidderdale Show in North Yorkshire.</desc>
<end>0550</end>
<title>Kirstie's Handmade Treasures</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0550</start>
<desc>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Al Murray joins Susie Dent in Dictionary Corner.</desc>
<end>0630</end>
<title>Countdown</title>
  </programme>
</channel>
