<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- produced for the bleb.org TV system at Sat Apr  4 07:21:45 2020 -->
<channel id="dave" source="XMLTV" date="09/04/2020">
  <programme>
<desc>Shopping from Home.</desc>
<start>0600</start>
<title>Teleshopping</title>
<end>0710</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Take a bow, humanity: Jake Yapp narrates this remorseless compilation of quite frankly the dumbest endeavours ever attempted on camera, most of which go hilariously wrong. S1 Ep39</desc>
<start>0710</start>
<end>0735</end>
<title>The Hurting</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>The Hurting</title>
<end>0800</end>
<desc>Take a bow, humanity: Jake Yapp narrates this remorseless compilation of quite frankly the dumbest endeavours ever attempted on camera, most of which go hilariously wrong. S1 Ep40</desc>
<start>0735</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>American Pickers</title>
<end>0900</end>
<desc>Whimsical US reality show following two pro pickers who root about for bargain buys. The boys visit a motorbike workshop and a warehouse with an underground bar. S5 Ep3</desc>
<start>0800</start>
<subtitle>Duck, Duck, Moose</subtitle>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>The fiercely competitive bargain hunters visit Barking, where Nat and John think they can smell a good buy. Two rivals unite when a vintage vehicle sparks a bidding war. S1 Ep9</desc>
<subtitle>Barking</subtitle>
<start>0900</start>
<title>Storage Hunters UK</title>
<end>0930</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1000</end>
<title>Storage Hunters UK</title>
<subtitle>Reading</subtitle>
<start>0930</start>
<desc>High stakes and high drama in the rowdy reality show! Barry and Darren are determined not to leave empty-handed from their own patch. Dan gambles as he tries to win big. S1 Ep10</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1000</start>
<subtitle>Manhattan</subtitle>
<desc>In Manhattan, Eddie Hall goes head to head with long-time rival Brian Shaw, pulling a 23-tonne truck - and attempting the notorious skyscraper `Monster' sandwich from Sarge's Deli. S1 Ep8</desc>
<title>Eddie Eats America</title>
<end>1030</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Eddie Eats America</title>
<end>1100</end>
<subtitle>Queens</subtitle>
<start>1030</start>
<desc>Stoke strongman Eddie Hall visits cosmopolitan Queens, NY, to make a solo attempt at a huge Greek kebab banquet, sample the best Chinese dumplings and try his hand at baseball. S1 Ep12</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1200</end>
<title>Top Gear</title>
<start>1100</start>
<desc>The fun-packed petrolhead show, hosted by Jeremy Clarkson and co. The chaps try to prove that a fly-drive holiday to Florida is more fun if you buy a car rather than rent one. S9 Ep3</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Red Bull Soapbox Race</title>
<end>1300</end>
<start>1200</start>
<subtitle>Best of Red Bull Soapbox</subtitle>
<desc>All the thrills and copious spills from the Red Bull Soapbox Race series, in which rival teams tested their gravity-powered vehicles against obstacle-littered courses. S4 Ep4</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Top Gear</title>
<end>1400</end>
<desc>High-speed high-jinks - and high trousers - with Clarkson and co, who are joined by pop mogul Simon Cowell. The lads race each other across London using a bike, a boat and a car. S10 Ep5</desc>
<start>1300</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1400</start>
<desc>It's all going downhill fast in the English capital, as teams of racers weave their gravity-powered soapboxes through an obstacle-littered course. Crashes ensured!</desc>
<end>1700</end>
<title>Red Bull Soapbox Race 2017: London</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Top Gear</title>
<end>1800</end>
<desc>Turbo-charged exploits with Clarkson and co. Here, there's a trip to find the best driving roads in Europe. The Star in a Reasonably Priced Car is the regal Helen Mirren. S10 Ep1</desc>
<start>1700</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Taskmaster</title>
<end>1900</end>
<subtitle>A Pistachio Eclair</subtitle>
<start>1800</start>
<desc>Richard Osman and Doc Brown are amongst the funny folk who have to impress a guy in gold chains: the Mayor of Chesham! Greg Davies sets the nutty tasks. S2 Ep3</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Rob Brydon hosts the comedy panel show featuring David Mitchell and Lee Mack. Rebecca Front and Jack Whitehall challenge Nick Hewer and Miranda Hart to tell fact from fiction. S5 Ep1</desc>
<start>1900</start>
<title>Would I Lie to You?</title>
<end>1940</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Would I Lie to You?</title>
<end>2020</end>
<start>1940</start>
<desc>Rob Brydon welcomes more wily guests to the deceptive comedy panel show. Joining captains David Mitchell and Lee Mack are Robert Webb, Sir Terry Wogan, Katy Wix and Kevin Bridges. S5 Ep2</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>2100</end>
<title>Would I Lie to You?</title>
<desc>Tall tales from celebrity panelists. Host Rob Brydon and regulars David Mitchell and Lee Mack welcome guests David O'Doherty, Katherine Parkinson, Bill Turnbull and Louie Spence. S5 Ep3</desc>
<start>2020</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>The posse meet three cat clerics who worship Lister. Lister vows to help them as they're being hunted by Rodon, the feral cat leader who wants to wipe out cats who worship anyone but him.</desc>
<start>2100</start>
<end>2300</end>
<title>New: Red Dwarf: The Promised Land</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>2300</start>
<subtitle>M-Places</subtitle>
<desc>Sue Perkins, Sami Shah, David Mitchell and Alan Davies join Stephen Fry on a trip to the Mountains of Kong, Mummerset and Brown Willy. Stop sniggering at the back. S13 Ep3</desc>
<title>QI XL</title>
<end>0000</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Taskmaster</title>
<end>0100</end>
<start>0000</start>
<subtitle>A Pistachio Eclair</subtitle>
<desc>Richard Osman and Doc Brown are amongst the funny folk who have to impress a guy in gold chains: the Mayor of Chesham! Greg Davies sets the nutty tasks. S2 Ep3</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0140</end>
<title>Would I Lie to You?</title>
<desc>Rob Brydon hosts the comedy panel show featuring David Mitchell and Lee Mack. Rebecca Front and Jack Whitehall challenge Nick Hewer and Miranda Hart to tell fact from fiction. S5 Ep1</desc>
<start>0100</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0140</start>
<desc>Rob Brydon welcomes more wily guests to the deceptive comedy panel show. Joining captains David Mitchell and Lee Mack are Robert Webb, Sir Terry Wogan, Katy Wix and Kevin Bridges. S5 Ep2</desc>
<title>Would I Lie to You?</title>
<end>0225</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0225</start>
<subtitle>Krysis</subtitle>
<desc>The useless mob reunite for the space comedy that's on another planet. The gang step in when Kryten has a mid-life crisis and changes his body cover to Ferrari red. S11 Ep5</desc>
<title>Red Dwarf XI</title>
<end>0255</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Red Dwarf</title>
<end>0325</end>
<subtitle>Dimension Jump</subtitle>
<start>0255</start>
<desc>The space-set comedy with a huge fanbase. Rimmer meets his charming counterpart from a parallel dimension. Needless to say, the pair don't get on very well. S4 Ep5</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Jaw-dropping sport stunts. Tim and Gendle devise a game of 'human hole in one', swapping golf balls for bikes, clubs for ramps and firing fearless riders at targets! S1 Ep5</desc>
<subtitle>Hole in One</subtitle>
<start>0325</start>
<end>0400</end>
<title>The Indestructibles</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Teleshopping</title>
<end>0600</end>
<start>0400</start>
<desc>Shopping from Home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0600</start>
<desc>Shopping from Home.</desc>
<title>Teleshopping</title>
<end>0700</end>
  </programme>
</channel>
