<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- produced for the bleb.org TV system at Sat Apr  4 07:22:46 2020 -->
<channel id="more4" source="XMLTV" date="09/04/2020">
  <programme>
<title>Teleshopping</title>
<end>0700</end>
<desc>Teleshopping.</desc>
<start>0350</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0700</start>
<desc>Teleshopping.</desc>
<end>0855</end>
<title>Teleshopping</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Kirstie's Vintage Gems</title>
<end>0915</end>
<desc>Kirstie Allsopp shows how forgotten furniture can be liberated from landfill, as she teams up with furniture maker Simon Bell to revive an old dining room chair.</desc>
<start>0855</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0915</start>
<desc>John and Julia are desperate to escape the cold British winters. Sara Damergi shows them what their £100,000 budget can buy in the Orihuela Costa area of Spain's Costa Blanca.</desc>
<title>A Place in the Sun: Winter Sun</title>
<end>1005</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1005</start>
<desc>Sandra is convinced that now is the time to buy her dream holiday pad in Torrevieja on Spain's Costa Blanca. Sara Damergi shows her a selection of properties for £45,000 or less.</desc>
<title>A Place in the Sun: Winter Sun</title>
<end>1105</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Find It, Fix It, Flog It</title>
<end>1210</end>
<start>1105</start>
<desc>Henry Cole and Max McMurdo restore and upcycle 2CV headlamps, a child's rocking horse, a Victorian streetlamp and a high chair. (S2 Ep12/25)</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1210</start>
<desc>Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien find, fix and flog unwanted possessions. At the fairground, the boys pick up a bicycle made for two, a ship's search lamp and a lambing chair. (S2 Ep13/25)</desc>
<title>Find It, Fix It, Flog It</title>
<end>1315</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1315</start>
<desc>Rebecca visits Angel for tips on renovating the kitchen. Amy and Marc transform a bathroom that's stuck in a 1970s time-warp. Ben and Billie prepare for Billie's brother's wedding. (S3 Ep4)</desc>
<end>1420</end>
<title>Escape to the Chateau: DIY</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Four in a Bed</title>
<end>1450</end>
<desc>The competition starts at Swallows Rest in Weymouth, Dorset, where owners Jane and Keith Smith are pulling out all the stops to win, but some of the feedback leaves Jane white as a sheet.</desc>
<start>1420</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1450</start>
<desc>The second visit of the week is to The Burley Inn in the New Forest where newly-weds Darren and James host, and guests Jane and Keith disagree over a toilet roll.</desc>
<title>Four in a Bed</title>
<end>1520</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>The third visit this week is to Hotel Montville in Redditch, Worcestershire, where host Ray Chowdhury hopes to win over his rival B&amp;B owners with his unique style and decor.</desc>
<start>1520</start>
<end>1550</end>
<title>Four in a Bed</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Four in a Bed</title>
<end>1625</end>
<desc>The last visit of the week is to The Silverton in Shrewsbury, where business partners Donna and David offer complimentary earplugs, but some guests are concerned about road noise.</desc>
<start>1550</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1655</end>
<title>Four in a Bed</title>
<desc>It's the last day of the competition and tensions are running high. Donna and David take umbrage with Jane and Keith, and accusations fly around the table before the winner is announced.</desc>
<start>1625</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>A blocked drain closes a seafood restaurant at the busiest time of the year. And have two new British pub owners in Spain done enough to make a future in the sun?</desc>
<start>1655</start>
<title>A New Life in the Sun</title>
<end>1755</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Tim and Fuzz take on the task of restoring a British pocket rocket - a 1997 Lotus Elise. (S7 Ep1/10)</desc>
<subtitle>Lotus Elise</subtitle>
<start>1755</start>
<end>1855</end>
<title>Car S.O.S</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1955</end>
<title>Escape to the Chateau: DIY</title>
<desc>Tim and Rebecca struggle to complete their kitchen. Ben and Billie welcome 60 guests. Dick and Angel's children Dorothy and Arthur help create a space for their gaggle of geese. (S3 Ep5)</desc>
<start>1855</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Grand Designs</title>
<end>2100</end>
<desc>Joe and Lina's clever space-saving low-budget build may be the smallest two-bedroom house you're allowed to build in London, but it'll be stylish, and theirs - not a landlord's. (Ep8)</desc>
<start>1955</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>2100</start>
<desc>...History in Your Back Garden: Brand new: Hugh Dennis and a team of archaeologists and experts descend on Florence Road in Maidstone, Kent, where they believe a Roman settlement is hidden.</desc>
<end>2200</end>
<title>New: The Great British Dig:...</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>2305</end>
<title>24 Hours in A&amp;E</title>
<start>2200</start>
<desc>Ten-month-old baby Amy is rushed to St George's after she stopped breathing. Expectant dad Craig has had a miraculous escape after falling 30 feet while motocross racing. (S8 Ep11)</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Documentary series telling the real stories behind dramatic and extraordinary calls made to emergency operators, including a tiger on the loose in Henry County, near Atlanta. (Ep1)</desc>
<start>2305</start>
<end>0010</end>
<title>Shocking Emergency Calls</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Jimmy Carr hosts. Sean Lock and Roisin Conaty take on Sarah Millican and Rhod Gilbert, while David O'Doherty joins Dictionary Corner with Susie Dent. With Rachel Riley. (S7 Ep8/17)</desc>
<start>0010</start>
<end>0115</end>
<title>8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>...in Your Back Garden: Brand new: Hugh Dennis and a team of archaeologists and experts descend on Florence Road in Maidstone, Kent, where they believe a Roman settlement is hidden.</desc>
<start>0115</start>
<end>0215</end>
<title>The Great British Dig: History...</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0215</start>
<desc>Ten-month-old baby Amy is rushed to St George's after she stopped breathing. Expectant dad Craig has had a miraculous escape after falling 30 feet while motocross racing. (S8 Ep11)</desc>
<end>0320</end>
<title>24 Hours in A&amp;E</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Food Unwrapped</title>
<end>0350</end>
<start>0320</start>
<desc>Favourite investigations. Kate and Helen explore vanilla, while in the Netherlands Matt explores the myth that Edam balls were once used as emergency cannon balls! (S17 Ep4)</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0350</start>
<desc>Teleshopping.</desc>
<end>0700</end>
<title>Teleshopping</title>
  </programme>
</channel>
