<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- produced for the bleb.org TV system at Fri Apr  3 07:19:14 2020 -->
<channel id="ch4" source="XMLTV" date="08/04/2020">
  <programme>
<title>Countdown</title>
<start>0550</start>
<desc>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Al Murray joins Susie Dent in Dictionary Corner.</desc>
<end>0630</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>The Executive's Executioner</subtitle>
<title>Cheers</title>
<end>0655</end>
<start>0630</start>
<desc>Norm's boss makes him an offer he can't refuse: accept a promotion or lose his job. So Norm finds himself in charge of firing other employees. (S3 Ep21/25)</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Cheers</title>
<subtitle>Cheerio, Cheers</subtitle>
<end>0720</end>
<desc>Diane decides to leave the bar and travel to Europe with Frasier. She wishes Sam would stop her from going, but he's too busy organising her farewell party. (S3 Ep22/25)</desc>
<start>0655</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0745</end>
<start>0720</start>
<desc>China Syndrome (Part 2/2): The last ever episode. On the flight to China, Doug and Carrie realise that home is where the heart is, but there's another surprise in store.</desc>
<title>The King of Queens</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>The King of Queens</title>
<subtitle>Pilot</subtitle>
<end>0810</end>
<start>0745</start>
<desc>US comedy about Doug, a New York postman who is king of his castle. Life is good with his loving wife Carrie and prized new TV, but then his recently widowed father-in law moves in.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
<subtitle>Robert's Rodeo</subtitle>
<start>0810</start>
<desc>When Robert is injured in the line of duty, Ray realises that he is partly, although unwittingly, responsible.</desc>
<end>0840</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>0910</end>
<start>0840</start>
<desc>When Debra discovers that Ray taped over their wedding video with the Super Bowl, he has to go to extreme lengths to make it up to her.</desc>
<title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
<subtitle>The Tenth Anniversary</subtitle>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Frasier</title>
<subtitle>Sweet Dreams</subtitle>
<end>0940</end>
<desc>Frasier puts his job on the line by refusing to read out an advertisement on air for the radio station's new sponsor.</desc>
<start>0910</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Frasier's unemployment situation brings about various emotional responses, including denial, anger and depression.</desc>
<start>0940</start>
<end>1005</end>
<title>Frasier</title>
<subtitle>Good Grief</subtitle>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1100</end>
<start>1005</start>
<desc>Gordon Ramsay visits Charlie's Italian Bistro in La Verne, southern California, where the decor is more authentically Italian than the soggy pasta on the menu.</desc>
<title>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Come Dine with Me</title>
<end>1200</end>
<start>1100</start>
<desc>In Sheffield, student Dylan - who lacks glassware and cutlery, and uses the top of his bin as a makeshift bar - takes on party girl Lynsey, confident Jamie and fashion designer Charlotte.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1305</end>
<start>1200</start>
<desc>Steph McGovern presents the brand-new daily programme live from her living room, with the latest information to help us navigate these unique times and special guest Jason Manford.</desc>
<title>Live: The Steph Show</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1305</start>
<desc>In Kent and Sheffield, the pawnbrokers consider deals on a signed David Bowie guitar, a pair of vintage cars, some rare high heels and an unopened bottle of champagne from 1952.</desc>
<end>1410</end>
<title>Posh Pawnbrokers</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1500</end>
<desc>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Al Murray joins Susie Dent in Dictionary Corner.</desc>
<start>1410</start>
<title>Countdown</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1600</end>
<start>1500</start>
<desc>Paul and Zung from Kent are about to realise their dream of moving to the Dordogne in France. Ben Hillman lines up five of the region's most stunning properties for their £300,000 budget.</desc>
<title>A Place in the Sun</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1700</end>
<start>1600</start>
<desc>Emma and Paul prepare for their biggest booking ever, Mariam and Johnno transform their chateau's grand salon, and Karen and Paul aim to transform the old stable and coach house. (S4 Ep13)</desc>
<title>Escape to the Chateau: DIY</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1700</start>
<desc>The third visit of the week is to Stoneleigh House Boutique Hotel in Buckingham run by friends Jane Parslow and Rachel Rawding. But can they impress despite forgetting their guests' names?</desc>
<end>1730</end>
<title>Four in a Bed</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>...Carry On: Jamie Oliver shows us some incredible recipes, tips and hacks tailored for the unique times we're living in. (Ep13)</desc>
<start>1730</start>
<end>1800</end>
<title>New: Jamie: Keep Cooking and...</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Homer's Enemy</subtitle>
<title>The Simpsons</title>
<desc>A new employee at the power plant who has struggled to build a decent life is incensed that someone as foolish as Homer could appear so affluent.</desc>
<start>1800</start>
<end>1830</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>The Simpsons Spin-Off Showcase</subtitle>
<title>The Simpsons</title>
<end>1900</end>
<desc>Troy McClure hosts a vision of the future of the Simpsons, in which Chief Wiggum becomes private detective Wiggum, P.I.</desc>
<start>1830</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Channel 4 News</title>
<end>2000</end>
<desc>Channel 4's flagship news programme. Including the weather.</desc>
<start>1900</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>New: Location, Location, Location</title>
<desc>In London, Kirstie gives Ros and Hannah the confidence they need to get what they want, and Phil helps Emma and Karthik, who have moved from Singapore, find their perfect home. (S34 Ep4)</desc>
<start>2000</start>
<end>2100</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>New: Coronavirus: How Britain...</title>
<start>2100</start>
<desc>...Is Changing - Dispatches: Dispatches investigates how the coronavirus outbreak is changing Britain in the long term, for better or worse, and from a fall in pollution to economic policy.</desc>
<end>2200</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>2230</end>
<start>2200</start>
<desc>Comedy about love and addiction. Mae apologises to her parents for her past transgressions as an addict. But if she's expecting anything in return, she's going to have a long wait... (Ep4)</desc>
<title>New: Feel Good</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>2230</start>
<desc>...for Stand Up To Cancer: The celeb bakers tackle a signature sandwich biscuit, a sweet bread-based technical and a cake showstopper revealing their favourite guilty pleasure! (S3 Ep5)</desc>
<end>2345</end>
<title>The Great Celebrity Bake Off...</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>A Day in the Life of...</title>
<start>2345</start>
<desc>...Coronavirus Britain: How is the country functioning under the shadow of the coronavirus? This film touches on the funny and the poignant, and gauges the impact of CV19 on Britain. [SL]</desc>
<end>0040</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</title>
<end>0135</end>
<desc>Gordon Ramsay visits Long Beach, California, to save a failing Italian family restaurant that opened in 1958 and is now under the misguided leadership of the eldest son, Nino.</desc>
<start>0040</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0135</start>
<desc>Professor Noel Fitzpatrick takes on an incredibly challenging case with Bella the injured boxer, who needs stem-cell scaffolding. A convoy of hedgehogs arrive with broken legs. (S9 Ep3/11)</desc>
<end>0230</end>
<title>The Supervet</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0230</start>
<desc>A young family take a sustainable, economical approach to creating a compact, simple and modest home on a shoestring budget at Ocean Shores in New South Wales. (S7 Ep5)</desc>
<end>0325</end>
<title>Grand Designs Australia</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Couples Come Dine with Me</title>
<start>0325</start>
<desc>In Wiltshire, Andrew and David host a ritzy affair, but Andrew's celebrity name-dropping fails to impress, and the guests are horrified by David's collection of Victorian hair clippings.</desc>
<end>0420</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Location, Location, Location</title>
<start>0420</start>
<desc>Kirstie Allsopp and Phil Spencer help two sets of first-time buyers who are struggling to find homes in Southampton and the New Forest.</desc>
<end>0515</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Beat the Chef</title>
<end>0540</end>
<start>0515</start>
<desc>A gastronomic gambler hopes to beat a seasoned pro with their version of fish and chips. Whose batter will be crisp and golden, and which chips are best - twice or triple-cooked? (Ep4)</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Kirstie's Handmade Treasures</title>
<start>0540</start>
<desc>At the Devon County Show, Kirstie Allsopp learns about beekeeping and beeswax candles, discovers the secret of home-made hand scrub, and tries her hand at crafting silver clay jewellery.</desc>
<end>0550</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0550</start>
<desc>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Al Murray joins Susie Dent in Dictionary Corner.</desc>
<end>0630</end>
<title>Countdown</title>
  </programme>
</channel>
